So in order to be a good friend you have to you know what Kate is right
I don't know what's wrong with psyche. He should have just left Alex alone. I spoke to her twice yesterday
I'm pretty sure everything was good. We had two long conversations and he's trying to start crap
I told him to stop to leave her alone instead of going at her about what she happened between them
So in order to be a good friend, you have to-
You know what, Kate is right.
I don't know what's wrong with Saiki.
He should have just left Alex alone.
I spoke to her twice yesterday.
Pretty sure everything was good.
We had two long conversations
and he was trying to start crap.
I told him to stop to leave her alone
instead of going at her about what happened between them.
And he keeps going on and on and on and screaming at her
and he's joining panels where he's not even wanted
and then they kick him out.
He was upset that, I guess, Sam and they kicked him
out of there and he didn't even like Sam
and he just goes on there to bitch.
And you know, Saiki, I told you, just leave it alone.
You're the one obsessed with her
and that's why she's reacting to you.
So and then you put on this crazy woman named Noel and you said you know her
I don't even know why she wanted to talk to me last week when I was on your panel because I don't know her and you knew
Oh Brandon, it's about Brandon and she was the accent. She put her
I will know her YouTube name in the back backstage or whatever and I don't even know what that was
So then she hopped back in on your panel yesterday
I guess or today. I'm not sure because I've been out and then all of a sudden you're playing an old
Video of Alex against me just because you're mad that you know, just leave her alone and stop making threats to her
You didn't go to any court or anything and you know that you're really messy you ban
Brandon because he was trying to take over your your live you said and complain about your music and then you ban them everything
No wonder she's upset with you. You go back and forth back and forth and you keep on just leave it alone
Get a job. Why don't you get a job?
Because you did ask for money, you know, and I'm not gonna lie about that
So you want me to go ahead and post videos that were more recent about you. You need to get a life
Anyway, this is Kate and everybody's against him right now and they're laughing because
he lost all these people and just going berserk and goes live after live after live making
videos of Alex.
And then the other day he's sitting there looking all sad, playing some other videos
of her.
You know, maybe just leave things alone and then you're talking about her everywhere
you go.
But anyway, this is Kate calling him out.
Turn a blind eye to supporting, platforming and promoting a legit predator.
She's talking about Brandon.
I guess he put...
That's what a good friend does.
Okay.
What do you need help with, Ashanka?
It's about psyching.
That's a good friend.
If you can get to things a little bit.
And I need to clear something up. He's lying about that Alex wanted to have him and pregnant her and have a baby
That's not at all. What happened. I know that what had happened was he was offering because she wants to have a kid
And sure he has somebody, you know, if she's gonna do it and he
He told her and we last about it. He told her that he would be willing
To give his you know, whatever so she can have a child
But he twisted it yesterday and he was saying that she wanted him to have sex with him and that way she gets pregnant
And she was just shocked because that's a lie psyche. She never told you that I remember what happened was
You offered her because she was talking about wanting to have a kid sometime and she's still
thinking about it, but she never asked you to give her your sperm, your liar. And her and I
spoke twice yesterday. Everything is cool. We unblocked each other on IG. And there you are
stalking her still. You're going on and on about her and you're joining panels and you got kicked
out of three panels. And then you've lost a lot of people. I mean, you didn't even have many people
in your chat, but this is Kate calling you out. That's really going on. That's the truth. Beautiful
I'm sorry, I don't have beautiful truths for you here, I have like, you know, I just have the truth.
The truth is not really pretty right now.
And they don't have my real number.
The truth is not pretty. What's going on?
Slander.
Hey.
Yeah, that's the truth. You're a liar.
Slander.
I think today, Concrete Larry asked me you guys to see the Concrete Larry, right?
You nasty Ashante.
Slander.
No, nobody's cool or anything else, but yeah, this is random.
Okay, but I'm zero people here, what's up Brandon?
Oh, just fighting a good fight, you know, yeah, I was just fighting a good fight, by the way.
Fighting a good fight, by the way, you know, and, you know, getting harassed by the same team.
Finally.
All of you is in the screen.
13 minutes in.
Oh, I must have Brandon blocked.
It's all basically.
13 27 seconds and he has his first person chat and chat psyche goes with who is drip feeding him money
Currently mayors and Brandon. He will stand on that hill until it stops. No, he said Brandon only gave him two five dollars
You know and I paid him a little more plus. I sent him some coffee
I say I also sent him 25 dollars and then sometimes he's asking for money. It's like it's about time. He get a job
I mean, what's he doing with his life being lucrative bingo?
bingo
You know, as soon as they figure out the truth, he'll be the most popular person.
I don't think anybody's named out of my mouth.
He's messy.
I'm obsessed.
Over a year, he's been sending people to my house.
Okay
He instigated it with beta 2 and then he puts it he made a tattoo of her
YouTube name and something about cats. I love cats or keys whatever her name is on YouTube and then later he decides
Things he's gonna get her mad by adding the word f u ck on top of that
Well, why did you even have the tattoo on it look pretty cheap like it was a three dollar tattoo
But yeah, so he did that it's like why put that on there. That's ridiculous
You think you're gonna hurt people but you're messy and you're jumping on all these panels and Kate you are so right about this guy
Now I've opened my eyes stone because he's messy and I told him leave her alone
and he just keeps going on and on and on playing videos no wonder she reacts. But as of yesterday
we're fine. You know I mean and then he's playing an old video from a few days ago. Yes we were
getting into it and she doesn't know anything about my family. We talked last night she knows more
but you know because she even agreed yes I know you know I take care of myself and me and my
siblings are very close. I was the one that used to protect them okay. You people don't know that
and we talk talk all the time and you know and they're always there for me and we hang out and
stuff so I mean this is ridiculous because you have nobody's psyche not one single person nobody
wants to do on their panels. You even joined Clonesy's panel to talk about Alex why don't you
Give her time and if she wants to talk to you, I'm sure she'll do that
You don't have to be messy and go on and on and on about her and then people complain about the AI music you keep playing
So let's see what um, what else that this person has to say about him. It's kate
Um, yeah, I mean it's a youtube has started demonetizing everybody if they use their thumbnails
Everybody AI if they do anything even though youtube has like all these AI tools that they originally used
They didn't want anybody that started demonetizing them to have their monthly money. They um now they're demonetizing for AI thumbnails
Buddy, I don't think that's why you're demonetized. They're
But go ahead and blame it on that
This is a picture like Alex has one person in her chat. Guess who it is Brandon
Well, she did it live about him, they busted him.
Yeah, she covered, she recapped it live about him being a predator and even called him a predator.
It's that live from a couple years ago, 2024, of him being a predator when he had vegan state his place when she was trying to get away from her ex, whatever his name was, I L something I don't remember.
And that's what she said and everybody that was, she was recapping somebody else's recap of that long live and you can see Brandon practically almost sexually assaulting this woman and vegan was trying to sleep.
And he would leave her alone and they started yelling and had an argument that video is out there because that's the one that I shared on my channel a year ago. No year and a half ago shared from K case channel.
So let's see what you guys messy it's like the hell. Okay Karen's calling me messy Karen, bitch. Oh my God. You know, messy. I'm messy. Okay, I have Brandon calling me a predator I have this bitch calling me messy.
I've always on economy all kinds of names.
They really deserve each other. I don't know how I ever got
lumped into this bullshit
But um apps
I will refute everything. Okay. What can you?
This these guys deserve each other. Oh my god
Get a job, dude. You don't shave. I mean you look like a method and everybody's saying you're doing meth
And it's obvious that you are get a life go do live go touch grass hang out with real people
You were kicked out of that gas station for trying to steal a coffee. I mean my god get a job
We brandon q show them dms that look like it had extremely obvious edits. Oh, yeah, it's used um
Oh, God, what's the name of the app?
It's an app, Mockly or something like that.
It's an app used to make fake DMs from all types of platforms.
I think it's called Mockly.
Well, no wonder because he made a fake don't know message to himself
St. Alex did it and it's obviously his writing because he can't spell right at all
And she was upset and she even posted on her community post that she didn't give him a no way a thousand dollars
And he's told us $4,000. Yeah, he's a liar. So he's making stuff up and gamble was right
He's got like a all his bots. Those are fake their bots. He doesn't have people in his chat
That's what they don't answer anybody and they keep repeating the same thing that he says over and over again all these different bots
So, I mean, this is sick, though, but he's making fake DMs now, too.
I can show all of his, and they're not fake.
The threats tell me to kill myself, you know, just because I joined Crystal's panel
when they wanted me up there to show me some video about him attacking a dog.
And Gamble was there.
No, I'm not judging you. I'm not judging you. Try um, try uh, you know a bath. I don't know. I'm sorry for your discharge
Who smokes cigars like cigarettes
Yeah, he doesn't even have litter boxes for all those cats in his place
He's I don't know how many cats he has and then a few of them disappear because he lets them in and out and you know
And I've even told him keep him inside if you're gonna keep him make it like a little you know take him out
You know if you want but get a little cat category thing outside so they're safe if you need to put him out for a little while
You know, be safe. I mean, my cats, they don't run out and I have four cats,
I'm gonna pick your knees.
I know you're just and then his carpet look horrible. I mean,
yeah, everybody clipped it. It's nasty looking. I mean, it's really bad.
And you know, he looks like a method and he's not shaving or bathing.
And then I don't know. I just never came across somebody like that.
I mean, let me tell you something. We're a real thing for me.
So I'm doing things on the count.
Is there anything else I know?
I know it's fucking.
But yeah, before I get too interested about it, I'm probably just going to say.
There's Sarah Summer, she gets banned because she mentioned Tony.
You cannot mention just Black Tony's name, you coward.
Talk to you at this point, it's like, I want to be in a stress, I want to be happy and in a good mood.
But anyway, I'll tell the truth, I had like 10 minute streams.
You don't tell the truth.
I don't know what to say.
But anyway, I guess no more.
He also had this woman that apparently he knows.
And when I was on panel with him, all of a sudden she's wanting to talk to me and ask
me for my link.
And I was confused like, who are you?
And then she put her name or something backstage like I was saying earlier.
And I didn't know her, so I didn't bother with that.
I just told him, I don't know who she is.
Oh, she's a nice lady.
She comes up and she knows Brandon because he tried to assault her or did assault her.
And he was saying, Karen, wanted to talk to you?
No, I didn't.
I said, you talk to her because I don't know who she is.
So he doesn't interview with her.
And she's got to be lying because she was laughing because she
said, what did he do to you?
Tell us what he did to you.
And then there was another lady that didn't know either one
of them in the background and saying,
she didn't know that woman either because that woman was
trying to talk to her.
She said, I don't even know you.
And so when he asked her about Brandon,
she said, yeah, yeah, he tried to show something to me.
And then the girl said, and then he said, a sexual assault.
And that other girl said, what?
A sexual assault?
And that goofy girl was smiling like it's funny.
You know you set that up though, right? Because that's your friend and I forget her no L. You said her name's no Ellen
And she pops up sometimes on your channel
Yeah, so have a good day guys. I'll see you when I see that
16 minutes 51 seconds and literally other than trolls that he blocked the only person in chat was Brandon Q
See that's all he had in chat. All right. Oh, he's live now
I got your number.
I got it.
Okay.
That's a W for Saki.
Oh, yeah.
Well, he'll just see what you're doing.
Yep.
I got it exactly.
That's it.
There you go.
I was confirmed.
All the way out all day.
So I didn't join panels or anything.
I did post it.
His man needs to shave and bathe and clean himself up.
He looks horrible compared to what he looked like when he first came on.
I don't know.
They showed a picture of him before.
And I will talk to you later at the time of your address.
It's obvious he's doing meth.
Or you can ask me.
Oh, he's going to add it.
What kind of losers those people are.
Exactly.
He's going to play a whole different video for anything.
On your Christmas tree, maybe.
Maybe.
And he's straight.
Who knows?
Yeah, such a victim.
Such a potential victim.
Yeah, right?
And he's victimizing people.
But again, this is like five seconds of a song.
You know, I thought it was weird that he popped up out of nowhere on IG trying to add me.
And I didn't even know him.
And I asked him, how did you find my IG?
Oh, I found you.
How?
Because I have a completely different name on my IG.
You're welcome.
You might not have found your IG is because I was friends with Vita last year, and so
it recommended because it recommends to your friends, but I didn't even have that many
friends on IG last year.
And then I didn't know who you were, I've never spoken to you, and you sort of leave
me messages, okay?
Remember this? And this is last year. This isn't just like, oh, I just tracked you down. And I had no idea who you were.
I had no idea of the car reversing or the drama. You got you contacted me when I was friends with Alex before I met.
Oh, shut up, candy kids. Get the fuck out of here. You're still a bitch.
Yeah, hold on one second. No, hold on. Maybe I have to read your whole message. Oh,
Okay, never mind candy kids. I love you. I'm sorry. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. I'll make you a mod. I'm so sorry.
I need to read the whole message.
I just struck out as like, read the whole message
instead of jump in the conclusions.
I'm a little bitch, jump in the conclusions.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Leave me that comment.
I'll be right back.
When we talked, me and Alex, yesterday we did talk twice.
She asked me, she said that she's not opening her chat sometimes when she goes live, or
do panels.
But she said, maybe we should do a panel just me and you.
And I said, well, I hope we don't talk about drama.
But I think it needs to be mentioned in what he's done.
I mean, people have lives, so Psyche, and I was pretty much out all day, it's Sunday.
And you don't even have any friends to hang out with, you know?
We were out.
I mean, you're ridiculous.
Get a life and stop talking about Alex and going on about, oh, she talks to my family
this and that, and then you're going to play an old clip.
What?
I'm messy. I play an old clip, but she talks to my family. Hello.
I think that was all that Kate had to say.
And that's a lot and I think she's framing I nice to me and me my dad as a suspect and I
Next told the police she would never do that
Because you know what I next isn't the one I took my patio set
No, I am about you one and Gia said don't do it and she made it
It was burn that the furniture she cried about it for a couple years and then she was over there
Talking to him again after that
So and I don't know what happened to burn now, but he was one that did it and he threatened to do it again later
When she pissed him off, so I don't know she just so you need to stop mentioning her names
I asked you to stop and you just don't
so is unbarred. Wait just a second until I finish this with Crystal. But I need to just like
This is old I think this is on IG I guess.
With Vita Vita told everyone to block me yesterday, and then she has a nerve to harass me and INX and I said Vita
What is going on? I just woke up like I'm like absolutely like one eye
She screamed at INX and INX said I want nothing to do with you two loser bitches
But then she blocked me but you know what Vita Vita you did say I've never harassed you ever ever
I guess it's no wonder that, uh, everybody on this, uh,
man, look at Wilbert, ready to chat.
Damn, Wilbert, ready to chat, so.
Can you watch, Vita? It's kind of strange.
Anyway, so I just want to kind of wrap all of this up.
So, I know.
I know.
My family and saying I killed my grandma because I did it.
In fact, all I ever said that you killed your grandmother,
what I said, and I think that this is very important
that you understand.
Crystal, do you want to go forward?
Yes.
I want to go forward for my family.
No, she won't be able to.
Well, I think it's very important that you understand.
that I knew that I need you to stop interrupting me please or else we're going to be here all night.
And I can't wait to say something real bad. So why I'm going to talk about that. Okay.
King, you're a POS who will arrest my dad two days before my grandma died. And that's what started it.
Okay, so are you going to finish without interrupting me? Okay. So I never said that you
killed your grandmother. I don't think that you killed your grandmother. I think that it was a
theory of the very unfortunate events where I mean you were like, you know, performing and all of that.
I don't believe that you were scared. I also believe you were worried.
And I believe you were scared and worried.
I don't believe you were scared because you were in the back of the room.
I don't care who calls out Astroma, I'm not going to be in any of this board.
She'll be able to talk to me when I think about it.
When I think about it, I'm not going to be in any of this board.
I'm not going to be in any of this board.
Oh my God, yo, these bitches crazy, my nigga.
They're like crazy too.
I feel like to be you, Chris.
Oh, you've done so much. Oh my God.
You are so stupid.
Oh my God, you actually thought...
But you know what, I have a picture of you and I'm gonna be back.
So her grandma passed, right?
May she rest in peace.
So did Crystal Anne take the grandma's house?
You know what I'm saying?
I don't know.
Because of the antique, you know, bedding and all that.
You know, once she passed, did Crystal Anne take over the house of the grandmother?
I'm thinking that's you guys.
I think people want to say, yeah.
Which would make sense.
She got a paid house, you know.
So there was her grandmother's shit.
No, I'm wrong.
Okay.
That ain't okay.
Come on down in the background.
All right, everyone, good morning, good afternoon, or good evening.
Something makes you pay for the crib, then.
Okay.
Whatever time it is, wherever in this world it is that you are.
Welcome once more to another live stream of IRL News Time Live.
I'm your hostess, Alexandra.
And before I close out my evening, I do want to go ahead and present the following
information to many of you in regards to someone known as Syke, aka the son of Judy
and Delos Bates, do not donate to him.
Do not donate to him. This is an official statement and an official warning in regards to the type of con artist and scam artist and master manipulator
That is this video is going to be forwarded to the Riviera center management and Riviera center properties legal team
Along with some other parties in the state of California
Because I'm not the first victim of the son of Judy and daily spades
Psych who is a public figure also known as John Bates
There have been other victims also.
He tends to prey upon people who are in the midst of grieving.
He preys upon the elderly.
He preys upon the mentally ill.
And he preys upon the just people
who are marginalized in society.
So when it comes to me, he was able to extract a little bit
over $1,000 from me, OK?
I will recover from that.
Of course, I work every day.
This is someone in regards to psych who is not employed,
not because he has any reason not to be employed,
but because he doesn't want to be.
And I've been employed for years and I have a great 401k plan. So I'm was taking a retirement and so I don't know I'm thinking about going back to work because it's boring. I do. I do go to that facility once a week on Tuesdays because it's like a I'm not getting paid for it for it to help them out with the activity room, especially since I made some friends over there that are still stuck there.
And so I go there is volunteer work for about for like three hours or so every every week, one day week. And that's what I do. But I'm probably thinking of going back to work. I don't need to I got enough on my 401k plan.
Everybody saw that I was making a lot of money and not only that our parents left us a lot of money
So and we're close all of us, you know, and they're my younger siblings
So we I'm definitely close with them. We talk every day and you know, they're always there and so I mean this is ridiculous
John you need to get a life. I mean gas station almost call the police on you for trying to steal a coffee
You need to get yourself together and start to stop, you know, you're making more drama
You were even on Sam and then they kicked you off and you got mad about that because your drama. Why are you there?
You know, you knew you had issues with them before
And then you were stalking Vita too. And that's why I remember Alex got mad at you, at how too faced you are, because you were already talking Vita after whatever blowout you both had.
So I don't want anything to do with you. I was busy all day. I didn't come back home till this evening.
And, you know, I went ahead and blocked you. I don't know why you ever added me on IG and it's just nothing but drama.
You go back and forth, back and forth with these people, and maybe give Alex a chance, you know, to cool off, because you keep making it worse by making these videos on her.
And I told you that twice the other day.
So let's go ahead and play some some of the rest of it. It's not all of it. He grew up in a very
affluent and wealthy family kind of situation. He thinks that he's too good to work. If you
look at the previous videos that I've made that outline his behavior, you'll see his behavior
is atrocious. He believes that he's entitled to stealing low dollar items from his local businesses
and whatnot. He treats people badly. He surrounds himself with very racist people, also very aggressive
people. But here's the most dangerous part about him. When he doesn't get his way with you, when
He has a group of people who, along with him, will stalk and harass you mercilessly.
They will do their best to stress you out, coerce you to suicide.
As of today, I received a threat from an associate of his who's a public figure,
known as Karen Latimer, aka IAnex, aka Grateful2026, who is saying that she's going to come by
allegedly where I live with a firearm and come right to-
No, because she had done a live and said she was going to come to my place,
which I've moved so nobody knows my new address,
and she was going to come with a body cam. That's what she said.
And then again, she said she was going to knock on my door.
what I said was I can protect myself. You know, she's here in Texas also along with me
and she knows what the law is here that we're able to protect ourselves our homes
and we are able to carry gun. I'm licensed so but I don't use my gun like that but if somebody's
threatening to come over you know to you know just to pop up in my place I have the right to
protect myself and that's what the police confirmed when I asked them about it so that's what happened
okay and it's on her live where she was she said it twice she was going to come over to my place
but yesterday her and I talked twice and and we talked for a long time both times and everything
So I don't know if it changed again today because I'm tired of the flip-flopping or people drinking and you know, and it's just
I don't know. I don't drink. I'm not a drinker, you know
Every once in a while I'll go out with friends and we'll have a margarita or two and that's it
But yeah, this this back and forth and I mean, but you know, it's like you get alive
Okay, you're going too far and everybody's hating you right now and all these
God all these streamers can't stand you right now and Kate isn't the only one
There's a few others that we're talking badly about you and they were thinking about you
Joining all these panels lately salmon's twice when they kicked you and then you went and made alive about it
You were all upset yesterday
my alleged apartment door.
Okay, this is not only something that law enforcement is going to be made aware of
But we talked about it yesterday not pretty much anyone and everyone okay now
This is from a couple days ago, and I went at her and she went at me
I mean online not in real life, so we talked about it yesterday, so I think everything's still cool
I don't know I don't like this back and forth at least people do though
You know you're drinking or some of them are on drugs and it's like they say one thing and then it's all back to the drum again
And I'm sick of it, but psyche I don't want anything to do with you
Don't ever try to add me again on IG you're shady and then you kept interrupting about this guy in ghost Tyler
He said you're his woman. I've never met the guy
And I already posted his him blowing me up all night long sending me links to join panels
We have lives and that's all he does all night long during these panels
And you know and I just told him to stop contacting me and then he thinks he's in love with me
I don't know this guy and then you were even saying it too and you bring him up. Oh, yeah
He's his woman. I don't know the guy. I've never seen him and he just put me in these panels
It was just weird because he gets kicked every time he joins those panels those people don't like them
There's some money. Oh my god. I love you ghost. I love ghosts. Oh my god. Ghosts you're the best. I love you ghosts.
Ghosts. Oh Mary ghost. You want me to marry you?
Yeah, this nut made a video about salmon and some other people that kicked them and he's all about this drama
He was bothering summer and she's cool. I sometimes watch her lives
She complained about how he was harassing her and she was busy because she does a lot of work outside of the internet
Like she helps with the homeless people and getting things done for them
She works with a team of people and she was busy and she said all he was doing was calling her about drama
I need you to help me with Alex Alex Alex and she said I am busy right now
And then he kept hitting her up a DM. She even read him
and she told him I'm busy and then he got upset because later on he saw her in Alex's chat.
So what? Dude, do life. I mean you're sitting there doing live after live after live on two or
three different channels. You already lost two of them. So this is him bitching about summer and
you know she does good work and helping the homeless and all of that and she does that a lot
every day. So this is what he has to say about her just because she wouldn't answer him immediately
to help him about Alex. What would she do? She couldn't do anything. I think she's okay with Alex.
So he just wants everybody to help him out immediately or whatever but listen to what he
You know actually yeah, if you want to hear that I mean I read the text messages
I mean I say I didn't ask for help with Alex at all
I asked about advice about doxing because she was doxed and asked for five minutes of her time
And it was over actually several several days not like you know, it wasn't like you know
Oh help me now. It was like over weeks of time
where she kept saying, oh, yeah, I'll come to your show.
Oh, you know, yeah.
And then it's like, and then she would like,
just like duck and dodge me, never came to the show.
So I confronted her on a show,
and then she wouldn't let me talk.
So that's why I was yelling that night.
So anyway, hi, Lola, how are you, baby?
Nice to meet you.
Well, I don't know.
I mean, I guess I missed INX's call yesterday
because I was taking in a lot of naps.
INX, you know, I know like, you know.
You can jump to conclusions and stuff, but we can play, you know, I and X talking to Brandon and stuff and like what they
How they talk and stuff. I mean, it's like this is not to be offensive to anything or whatever. It's just like
interesting I think
This video is still up, but you know, I don't know. I didn't grab it in time, but I see I
Did ask, you know trip trip and sip for help and he said, oh, well, he asked me for help. So I'm not gonna do it
That other people were asking for I wonder if he'll do it now because other people are asking. That's not me
Like I'm some kind of like I don't deserve like you know
anything
Any consideration about it? Let me see. Well, where's this?
diverse death cults
See
Irrifying if you dwell on it too much right because we usually think of the internet with this expectation of like
flawless precision. You know, you send an email and it leaves an exact time stamp.
Exactly. Or you post a photo and the metadata just locks in your location forever.
Yeah.
We really like to comfort ourselves with this idea that the digital world is this perfectly mapped grid of binary code.
Like it's a reliable, permanent record of who we are and what we do.
And it gives us a sense of control, right? If everything is documented and searchable, we just assume the truth is always going to be a few clicks away.
But then you step into the world of internet live streaming communities.
Oh boy. Yeah.
that is a whole different reality. It really is. Specifically, if you look at the raw, totally
unmoderated frontier of it, you realize that the mapping system is completely broken. It's not a
clean grid at all. Not even close. We are looking at an absolute psychological wilderness, like
alliances shift by the hour, identities are shielded behind dozens of burner accounts.
routinely spirals out into devastating, irreversible, real-world consequences.
It is wild, and that intersection is exactly where we are taking you today in this deep dive.
It is the absolute definition of diagnostic muddy waters.
You have highly sophisticated technology masking some...
incredibly broken human psychology. Exactly. And our sources for this deep dive are a massive
stack of transcripts compiled from a YouTube channel called IRL Newstime, which is hosted by
a commentator named Alexandra, right? Yes, Alexandra. And she has spent months methodically
cataloging hours of leaked voicemails, live stream recordings, and, you know, just endless
digital receipts from the specific community. It's a huge undertaking. But before we really
start unpacking all of this, we should probably add a quick disclaimer for everyone listening.
dealing with some incredibly heavy legally charged material today.
Very heavy. We're talking allegations of elder abuse, severe harassment, and even suicide
coercion.
Right. So we are simply analyzing the claims and the fascinating, albeit really dark, human
behaviors that are documented in Alexandra's files. We aren't endorsing these as legal
verdicts.
Right. We're just using them to understand a very specific, very modern phenomenon.
And what the source material documents is basically a master class in how vulnerabilities are exploited online.
It really is. This isn't just regular internet beef. It's this highly complex ecosystem where emotional desperation meets predatory opportunism.
which brings us to the main focus of this deep dive.
Yes. Our primary mission today is to unravel the psychological puzzle of one central figure in this community.
She is an older woman, primarily known online as Karen.
Though she operates under a dizzying array of aliases, like INX, Grateful 2026, Dana, Piki Cartel, it's hard to keep track.
it is. And we are going to map out her deeply erratic mental state, the absolute whirlwind of
contradictions in her public claims, and really explore how her profound offline isolation has
trapped her in a toxic, financially abusive web.
specifically with two younger internet personalities, Brandon and Psyche.
Yeah. The story of Karen, or INX, is ultimately a tragic case study. It shows us what happens when
severe cognitive decline collides with the permanent predatory nature of the internet.
Let's start with who Karen actually is when she logs off, because I mean the contrast between
her digital avatar and her physical reality is just staggering.
It's day and night. According to the IRL Newstime Transcripts, Karen is around 66 years old.
and she has a self-admitted criminal record dating back to 1982.
Which we are definitely going to dive into later because her explanation of that record
is a psychological rabbit hole all on its own.
Oh, absolutely.
But the first major red flag that Alexander points out in the sources is Karen's visual abscess.
Right. She never turns her camera on during these live streams.
Exactly. She's spending hours and hours a day on visual platforms,
interacting with highly visual content creators, yet she remains this disembodied voice.
And she claims this is just a preference, right, like she just values her privacy.
That's what she says. But Alexandra's analysis of the audio suggests something much more vulnerable.
Karen is likely actively hiding her physical environment.
Like her actual living situation.
Yes, specifically, she's hiding the presence of physical caretakers.
Which makes total sense when you look at the health crises she describes.
I mean, there is a voicemail from May 2026 that is incredibly dark.
It's hard to listen to.
She leaves this frantic message for Alexandra detailing a near-death experience from July of 2025.
Yeah, she says she contracted sepsis, she was in the ICU,
and she literally tells Alexandra she was given
quote, eight days to live. I mean, sepsis in an individual in their mid 60s is a catastrophic event
for the body. The systemic inflammation can cause lasting neurological and physical damage.
And she talks about spending months in a rehabilitation facility, just relearning the
mechanics of walking. Yeah. And in another voicemail, she literally describes herself
crawling around her apartment.
Crawling. That just paints a picture of a woman who is physically trapped.
Completely trapped. But here is where the source material takes a much darker turn.
Alexandra repeatedly points out that Karen isn't just suffering physically.
Right. The transcripts of her voicemails strongly suggest she is exhibiting the early signs of
Alzheimer's or dementia.
And we aren't just making a clinical leap here. We are looking at textual documented evidence
of a mind slipping.
What's the main symptom they talk about? Looping, right?
what the streaming community calls looping.
Neurologically, this is when short-term memory
fails to record recent events.
So she just repeats herself.
Exactly, it causes the individual
to repeat the same grievances, the same stories,
or the same questions continuously,
entirely unaware that they just had
the exact same conversation five minutes prior.
That is so sad.
But it's fascinating how the internet functions
as a surrogate reality for someone in that state.
Oh, completely.
Think about her situation. She's physically frail, isolated in an apartment, possibly relying on caretakers.
The physical world has essentially stripped her of her agency.
So she logs on, she takes whatever financial resources she has.
Yeah.
And she literally buys her way into the lives of these younger streamers.
Because the digital world offers the illusion of omnipotence.
Yes.
When your physical reality makes you feel powerless, invisible, or burdensome,
the internet offers a completely different interface for existence.
You know, I kept visualizing the Wizard of Oz while reading these transcripts.
Oh, that's a really good comparison.
Right. Karen desperately wants to project this omnipotent, terrifying presence online.
She wants to be the great and powerful Oz, pulling the levers, hoarding everyone's secrets,
dictating who fights with whom.
I didn't think that Factor could help me reach my protein goals, boy was I wrong.
Free high protein breakfast for a year?
Yeah, that's real.
Every meal is loaded, ready in minutes and tastes unreal.
I don't have to track macros or plan meals.
Factor does it all for me.
But when you pull back the curtain, it's just a fragile, lonely individual whose own internal
control panel is violently short-circuiting. I take that analogy a step further, actually.
The tragedy of Karen's situation is that the cognitive bandwidth required to be the puppet
master, you know, to track the lies, manipulate the alliances, maintain the leverage,
is the exact cognitive function she is actively losing.
Wow.
Yeah, it requires immense mental agility to run a successful manipulation campaign and her hardware is failing
Which brings us to the absolute chaos that failing hardware creates
Because Karen can no longer keep track of her own narrative. She is constantly contradicting herself and on the internet where everything's recorded in time
Stamped. Yeah, this leads to a massive publicly documented web of lies. Let's break down what I call the voicemail paradox
because this is just wild. It really is. So Karen will go onto these public live stream panels
where hundreds of people are listening and she'll declare I do real life. She insists she doesn't
obsess over the internet. Right and she specifically adamantly claims she never leaves voicemails for
Alexandra. But the physical evidence contradicts her entirely. Alexandra's phone has a blocked
folder brimming with dozens of frantic rambling voicemails from Karen. Stretching all the way back
I'm trying to picture this interface. Alexandra is hosting a live stream,
displaying her phone screen to her audience, and literally playing these voicemails out loud
while Karen is in the same chat claiming they don't exist.
Yes, Alexandra is playing the receipts in real time.
Yeah.
And Karen's denial isn't necessarily a calculated gaslighting attempt.
You think she just doesn't remember?
It may very well be a genuine inability to remember leaving them.
Because of the cognitive decline that is so jarring then you have the I don't record lie
Which I think highlights the intense paranoia associated with all this. Oh, this one is wild Karen leaves a voicemail for Alexandra
swearing up and down
I didn't record you, you were my friend.
And the tone is incredibly convincing,
like she sounds so genuine.
But within that exact same timeline
on the exact same topic,
she pivots to threatening Alexandra.
She says she's going to release secret recordings
she made of their conversations.
Yes, and then in a third voicemail,
she completely breaks down and admits,
I'm sorry I lied and recorded you.
It's a total short circuit.
Denial, threat, and confession all mashed together in a matter of days or hours.
But I think the most glaring example of this has to be the 1982 arrest story.
Okay, let's unpack this slowly because I genuinely need help making sense of the psychology here.
It's a lot to untangle.
So Karen leaves a voicemail trying to explain a decade's old criminal record.
She starts by saying she had a boyfriend named Orlando.
Right.
He had drugs in their apartment,
they threw a party, they got busted.
And she claimed she was sent to a treatment center
in Kingwood for 60 days to get clean.
Which is a very coherent narrative.
It frames her as a young woman caught up
with the wrong crowd, dealing with substance abuse.
It garners a certain level of sympathy.
Right, it makes her sympathetic, you feel bad for her.
But then, literally mid-story,
without even pausing for breath,
she completely changes the narrative.
She suddenly says, wait, no.
They didn't charge her for the drugs.
Yeah, she says she was actually put on probation for harassment because she filed a
false police report against someone who owed her boyfriend money.
I am so confused by this.
It is baffling.
If she is a seasoned manipulator and the source even calls her a career
criminal, why on earth would she admit to filing a false police report?
It entirely destroys her credibility today.
Exactly.
If you are trying to convince the internet that your enemies are committing crimes,
admitting you have a history of lying to the police is the absolute worst thing you could do.
Is she just a terrible liar or is something else happening?
This is where we have to look at the neurology of a failing mind.
Think of her brain like a computer where the RAM, you know, the short-term working memory
is completely failing.
Okay.
She cannot remember the narrative she established two minutes ago.
The deep-seated muscle memory of being a lifelong manipulator and survivor.
That is still intact, so she's running off instinct. Yes
Her brain keeps running the manipulation software trying to find whatever lie gives her the most immediate leverage or
Excuses her behavior in that exact second
So she starts with the drug story
Realizes maybe it makes her look weak or something and her brain immediately generates a new excuse the false police report without realizing
How damaging that new excuses to her overarching credibility exactly she has the instincts of a predator
but the execution of someone trapped in a deep cognitive fog.
We see this play out in her online relationships too.
Oh, definitely.
Like her obsession with that streamer named Crystal Anne.
Yes.
Karen goes on public panels and loudly declares her hatred for Crystal Anne.
She calls her crazy, demands that people stop associating with her and claiming she wants
absolutely nothing to do with her.
Yet, Alexandra's transcripts show Karen spending hours lurking in Crystal Anne's live streams.
She calls her relentlessly.
It's an all-consuming obsession wrapped in a thin veneer of disgust.
She lacks the impulse control to stay away from the conflict.
It's like the trauma is the only thing tethering her to the world.
That's a great way to put it.
And this vulnerability, this desperate, messy need for connection and control,
it sets the stage for the most disturbing dynamic in the source material.
Because Karen is physically isolated and cognitively slipping,
she is drawn to some of the most volatile figures in the live streaming space.
Which brings us to Brandon Quintana.
It was a gift. I resented it for three weeks, then I filled the bowl with water, dropped the grapes in and I just
I wasn't ready for that. I watched my daughter eat half a bowl of grapes this morning before I used it.
Just rinse them under the tap the way I've done for six years, the way everyone does, the way that doesn't actually do anything.
Bowl of water, drop the pure pot in, one button, walk away.
I came back in 10 minutes. The water was brown. Not a little cloudy, brown. And here's the part that stopped me.
That color is not dirt.
It's not the skin bleeding into the water.
It's the pesticide residue,
leaving the fruit for the first time,
pulled out by the ions,
sitting there in the water
where I could actually see it.
That's what I'd been handing her every morning
and calling it clean.
no chemicals, no scrubbing, no refills, the charge last weeks.
Here's something nobody's told you about the price.
Three in the morning, we got a one star review.
Woman said it works, but she almost didn't buy it
because of the cost.
My boss read it at 6 a.m.
He didn't call anyone, he just pulled up the pricing
and said, free shipping, 70% off, effective immediately.
You've handed someone you love a piece of fruit this week
and called it clean.
You already know what I'm about to say.
That discount is live right now.
Go get it before he changes his mind.
My butchery goal just kicked in sir. That is always an immediate yes for me
My husband has been initiating the bedroom again, and it is all thanks
to Bluetooth gold.
Bluetooth gold.
We weren't sure if gold was actually worth the upgrade.
After the night we just had,
he is not going back to the generic stuff.
It's a game changer because it gives you passion
and performance all in one tablet.
There's no performance anxiety.
It's just connection.
Bluetooth gold focuses on arousal.
So you'll get the strongest physical response
with the mental drive to back it up.
Bluetooth makes us still Denifil and Tildalafil
to take care of the physical side
with apomorphine and oxytocin.
to target the brain.
So it's a powerful four-in-one combo
for harder, longer-lasting erections.
So we're talking three times stronger,
five times faster, and lasts up to 36 hours.
Watching him take luchu gold is refreshingly simple.
One tablet under the tongue, no stress, no over thinking.
Once you feel it, you notice the difference.
Connection is key, guys.
All in one.
It's not just about the physical,
but it's getting him actually in the mood.
Bridging the gap between your mind and your body.
So you can just relax, stay in the moment.
and go the distance.
Confidence isn't something you outgrow.
With Bluetooth Gold, it's something you upgrade.
The process has never been easier to get it.
It's all done 100% online and shipped
discreetly to your door.
If there's one thing that I'd recommend
to married couples, it's this.
Bluetooth Gold.
Connection is key, you guys.
Experience it for yourself with Bluetooth Gold.
So I wait by two months, get one free at Bluetooth.com.
And this dynamic is an absolute psychological powder kick.
To understand how explosive this is, we have to look at who Brandon is.
He's roughly 30 years younger than Karen.
Right. He's in his mid-30s. She's in her mid-60s.
And the source material paints a grim picture.
He has severe behavioral and anger issues.
Furthermore, the transcripts detail accusations from within the community
of him speaking inappropriately with minors.
He is considered a highly predatory figure, but Alexander offers a very specific cultural
and psychological key to understanding Brandon.
The video game.
Yes.
She links his erratic behavior and his savior complex to a game he obsessively streams called
Pragmatata BF6.
The details of this game are fascinating.
It's a sci-fi game where the main character, a soldier named Hugh, is tasked with rescuing
and protecting a child-like android named Diana.
and Alexandra theorizes that Brandon heavily projects himself onto this soldier protagonist.
He views himself as a heroic savior whose mission is to protect innocent childlike entities.
But when that digital fantasy bleeds into his real-world interactions,
it translates into a deeply unhealthy predatory fixation on actual young girls.
Exactly. He justifies his boundary crossing by telling himself he is protecting them.
And into this deeply blurred, volatile reality steps, Karen,
she develops this bizarre attachment to Brandon.
The sources describe it as this confusing, toxic blend
of a romantic crush and a maternal mother-son dynamic.
Yeah, they spend hours on the phone
while he plays Pragmatata BF6 on his live stream.
She is essentially buying his time.
She is fulfilling her profound need for companionship,
and he's a captive audience willing to listen
to her looping grievances.
But she doesn't just want companionship, does she?
No, she wants a weapon.
Right. She wants a proxy soldier to fight her battles for her because she won't turn
her own camera on. So she starts feeding Brandon, highly damaging entirely unverified intel about
other women in the community that she considers enemies.
And she knows exactly what buttons to push. She tells Brandon that streamers like Big Trollah
which is such an extreme allegation. She takes Brandon's known psychological fixation,
his twisted desire to save children from predators, and points it directly at her personal rivals.
She hands him an explosive, fabricated narrative, assuming he will be her silent, loyal assassin.
But this is where the cognitive decline really betrays her. She completely fails to assess
totally. He entirely lacks the social calibration, the subtlety, or the discretion to play
the covert game Karen thinks they're playing.
There's an incredible moment documented in the transcripts that perfectly captures this backfire.
Oh, the speakerphone incident?
Yes. Karen and Brandon are talking.
Karen thinks it's a private conversation, but Brandon, lacking any filter, starts repeating
these horrific allegations about Big Trollah and Eliti Petty out loud directly to his live
stream audience.
And Karen suddenly realizes she is on speakerphone.
She realizes hundreds of people are listening and, more importantly, that the stream is
being recorded.
Augustrating a smear campaign panic instantly sets in you can hear it. She tries to backpedal in real time
She starts playing dumb saying things like oh, I didn't know about drugs. I just know what she said
She's trying to distance herself from the fire. She just lit but Brandon is not having it
He completely throws her under the bus on the live stream. He starts yelling at her. What do you mean?
You're the one that told me. Why are you acting like she didn't do that? You told me?
It's a stunning collapse of her entire manipulation strategy, and what we were witnessing in that exact moment is a massive shift in the power dynamic.
Walk me through that shift, because up until this point, Karen seems to be the one running the show.
Initially, Karen holds the leverage. She has the financial resources, which she uses to buy attention, and she is the purveyor of the information.
You know, the gossip she's hoarded over years of lurking.
Right. She's the provider.
Which puts her in a position of authority over Brandon.
But the second Brandon repeats those secrets on a recorded livestream,
and the second he explicitly confirms that she was his source,
the leverage completely flips.
Because now he has the evidence.
Exactly.
Brandon is now holding the tape.
He has documented undeniable proof of First Lander.
The asset she thought she was commanding has instantaneously become a massive, unpredictable liability.
He holds her secrets. Therefore, he holds the power. She is suddenly entirely at his mercy.
And Brandon, despite his behavioral issues, is incredibly quick to realize this.
He knows he has her cornered, which transitions us into the most cynical, predatory aspect of this entire situation.
It gets so much worse.
Yeah.
Once Brandon realizes Karen's vulnerability, like how terrified she is of being exposed and how desperate she is to maintain his favor,
he teams up with another major figure in the community to systematically drain her finances.
Enter Psyche, also operating under the name John Bates.
The source material is brutally straightforward about Psyche.
Alexandra describes him as an active substance addict and a master manipulator.
His entire online presence is essentially a digital front for extortion.
Yeah, the transcripts show how he falsely claimed to have had a romantic relationship
with Alexandra solely to boost his own profile and siphon viewers from her audience.
He identifies people with resources or clout, attaches himself to them, and bleeds them dry.
It's highly calculated so when psyche and Brandon realized that Karen is the perfect mark
She's paranoid and she has a little bit of money
One would think a global pop sensations. Zara Larson doesn't have to think about money. No, but we follow her
It is
Like a white woman with a big arm
They coordinate their efforts they start running these elaborate good cop bad cop routines on her
Let's break down one of the specific scams
They run because the mechanics of it are fascinating the source is referred to it as the auction scam
It plays perfectly on her paranoia and her need to control the narrative
Okay, so psyche will be hosting a public live panel. He will privately contact Karen and tell her hey
Brandon just paid me $100 to come up on the stage
and talk trash about you to my audience.
Which immediately triggers her fight or flight response.
She cannot stand the idea of being spoken about
without being able to defend herself or control the screen.
So panicking, Karen will immediately send Psyche $100
of her own money to match the bid
just to secure a spot on the page.
So let's have one night that she said
she didn't want Brandon on, I was like,
well, and then Brandon is sort of staying backstage.
She's like, I'll pay you 20 bucks.
And then she's like, I'll pay 30 bucks.
And then he was like, I'll pay 50 bucks.
And then he eventually said, I'll pay 100.
You pay 100 bucks.
And she goes, no, I'll match it.
And so I didn't let him on.
And then she's like, well, I didn't know how that worked.
I don't know.
And so I was just like, we'll just forget about it.
But you know what?
I'll give you these 10 tokens or whatever to clap.
And so that's what she had.
But she never paid me anything for that.
So anyway.
panel to stop Brandon from talking.
But the underlying reality, of course,
is that Brandon never had $100 to give Psyche.
It's a phantom bid.
Completely manufactured scarcity.
It's insane.
Brandon and Psyche coordinate this lie
to create a crisis out of thin air, trigger Karen's anxiety,
and extract her money.
They are also highly adept at weaponizing her jealousy.
The transcripts detail another instance
where Brandon manipulates the user interface of his streaming
platform to extort her.
Oh, the power chat thing. How does he weaponize that against her?
So Brandon will be streaming and he will use a system called the power chat,
which is a feature where viewers can pay money to have their messages highlighted on the screen.
Right. Pretty common on these platforms.
But Brandon logs into his own system using an alternate account
and fakes a $1,000 donation to himself.
Wow.
He labels the donor as anonymous.
Then, while live on the air, he heavily implies to his audience that the anonymous $1,000 came
from Alexandra, the host of IRL News Time.
Hi, Godbody, what's up?
And he does this specifically because he knows Karen is watching.
What's up, Godbody, what's up?
You want to come up or just play about it?
Well, I have stuff to tell you, though, but yeah, thank you for coming.
Everyone's subscribed to GodbodyRainz and for the link up.
What's she doing?
I don't know.
Okay, here, I'm gonna put the,
everyone wants to come up and they can ask about,
but I mean, it's just like so, so crazy, you know?
I, she had texted yesterday.
She's the man.
It's like, she's in a good mood.
And so I just didn't get back to her
because I've been like smoking this vape
and it makes me sleepy.
It has three different kinds of weed in it.
And I got so drunk last night and I was like, you know,
and I can kick off the Sandman show.
I went on, I leapt on my own.
I thought I got kicked off once,
but somebody else got kicked off.
And so I didn't even get kicked off of this show.
But then I wake up today, oh, psyche's a lie.
Oh, no, not another, like, and it's like,
wow, just talk to me first.
I mean, it's like, because it's like, no.
She's not a bad person.
I actually did see her.
She's not like, I mean, she's not like hundreds of pounds
or anything, and she's not like in a wheelchair.
I mean, I said, I've been honest yet.
I said, she looks like, you know, Liza Manelli.
You know, I mean, I don't even know how else to put it.
She had that like short black hair
and kind of like a happy attitude.
She was walking by a nice jacuzzi
that was closed that day, I think.
She said, I don't know.
That's all I got from the conversation.
She showed me for like two seconds.
So that was it, you know, but she's a nice lady, you know?
I don't know. And then Alexander was on this thing yesterday.
She was like on Kate and saying, oh, well, psyche.
Like, you know, here's when we met.
He was like, you know, he didn't talk very much.
And he, well, big girl, he didn't talk very much.
He like, you know, well, I was like introverted.
And then I fell asleep in the car the next day.
And I wasn't like real excited.
Like, and like all into shooting because I was tired.
And I was like, I don't know.
She's like she's I don't know and that and then she keeps saying that she
Yeah, Liza Manelli is on the modern day. I think she's alive, right? No
Yeah, she keeps saying she should pick the restaurant. So she didn't have my address beforehand. Okay, did she I think by this point
She didn't have my address. She could have it was Doc's and stuff, but I remember
She's like, well, where should we have dinner?
I said, there's a restaurant that I used to go to with my family right up the street.
It's like walking distance from my house.
I can like walk over there literally when you get there.
And it's called Hutties.
It's called the Hudson House, but by Hutties.
And so she didn't like do all the research and figure it out.
She even had my address then.
I told her where I would be like, you know, and so I met her at the restaurant.
And then we went to my house because I was going to grab a couple beers and we were going
to go hang out at her motel or whatever.
And it's like, and I didn't feel like letting her up because I feel like she's probably snoopy and I didn't want her snooping around or whatever, you know, or like, you know, I was taking a picture when I went to the bathroom or something and all of a sudden in my, I don't know, I just didn't trust it.
So I just let her outside for like two minutes when I rang out the beers.
We really did a 10 minute like walk around the block and she like walked really fast and was like we were like running basically on the block
This is the night before the Hollywood thing and then
Basically
Yeah, until the next day. Yeah, I think she got me breakfast. I think she got me McDonald's or something like that
I think a copy from McDonald's, but I fell asleep in the car and
We went to Hollywood and I've been to Hollywood and it's like to me. It's like kind of a street
It's kind of like, you know, it's kind of like dirty a little bit and not like I mean
It was fun when I was a kid that there was like, but there's like some guys just like spider-man
It's just we got down syndrome just like spider-man and stuff. I mean, it's like it's like not kind
It's kind of like scary to me
But I went, and your phone crashed, you can come up on a panel link if you want, but yeah.
But anyway, yeah, so...
I forgot my story, but yeah, I've been smoking this weed.
Let me see.
It flipped flop.
Oh, hold on.
Big bits, big bits.
Make sure you turn in to talk your ish
to Christians and the Exposed.
I know.
Well, I went off on summer end and I was like,
you know, and Katrina yelled at me.
It's like, yeah, maybe it's like, you know,
I shouldn't like be asking any favors from anybody.
I asked for five minutes of time.
It was just kind of like, I said, oh yeah, well,
I don't want to get involved.
I was like, I'm trying to get you to do a bump.
I'm asking, I want to ask you a question about like.
Doxing I have pregnant Alex. I'm not lying. She did ask for my sperm like and I've told people
behind the scenes so they know about this.
But it was like, I wasn't telling everybody
but there are episodes where she alludes to it.
I can like show you Alexander McQueen was on.
He was saying, he wanted to give this permit.
She's like, well, wait, what if Psyche impregnated me?
And then Alexander McQueen can marry the daughter
or something like that.
I was just sick and I was like, what?
I didn't understand.
I thought it was just maybe joking and stuff,
but I mean, yeah, but no, she did ask.
She said like, you know, and she didn't say like something about us having sex too, and I was like, well, I don't know about that
I thought it would be like, you know, you just go into like a little clinic
And then I was looking at a game game to know if you're looking at
My favorite YouTube star. No, I'm just kidding. Um, no
No, I don't know if she would have sent me a car
It's a really hard for me to not to get to not get into like a car that's paid for me
But what but then what if it takes me to like, you know, she needs a turkey bait?
I know I think I thought she I thought she had eggs on I didn't know how it worked. I don't know
Yes, she might have been used a turkey base there. She might have done some kind of black magic ritual
On the tennis court. I don't know that was the first movie. The first movie I saw of her was on the tennis court
it was
I've watched it with people, too.
And they wanted to watch the pegging.
It was like these Latino people,
and they're like, oh, it was a Latino guy and a black woman.
And they're like, oh, pegging, pegging, pegging.
They're like, look, she's pegging right there.
And I was like, okay.
And I watched that.
And so that's what I saw when people came to my house.
And nobody, we just watched, we didn't get it.
If you didn't think it would be on that, we were just like, I don't know, I don't, I wasn't, I wasn't, I don't know, it was an arousal, it was fear, fear, confusion, no, I'm just, I don't know.
Um...
But she's saying she's gonna leave the internet when I first met her
She was like, I'm doing it and I get three more days on
This show and she's like and then I'll be I'll be gone into the wind, you know, I'll be gone in the sunset and
Yeah, she said I won't be covering these drama communities anymore. I just might do my Bibles. My hair is glorious. Well, thank you so much
Yeah, thank you. I like yeah, I have a down today
Well, people say I'm bald and stuff like that, but hey, this guy, this guy, if you want to see a good looking bald man, God, while you're raining, it's a great looking bald guy, great.
I mean, if I was bald, I wouldn't want to look like him. He's his perfect, perfect head.
He does. Everybody, make sure you subscribe to him. That's his name on YouTube.
And he's very, besides like, you know, very good looking, he's very like, you know.
He's like a caveman in the modern day, kind of like that kind of personality.
And he's from, I think from Boston, or Boston or around like the back east or something
like that.
And he's just like, he's very cool.
She always says that.
Yeah.
She wanted to remake.
She wanted to remake the cosplay porn.
Did they really need to make it in the first place?
Mercury is retrograde so they might be fighting. Yeah, I mean it's like that communication gets bad. You live in New Jersey
Okay, New Jersey. Okay. Yeah, I don't know I have bought I have Boston people and I've been fighting with this woman named Boston Bridget
Oh, yeah, but if you post your link to I mean it's like to your mod you can post
You post your link if you want. I mean, it's like but it's just God while you reigns if you just search that
the name everybody it will come right up and
Probably my I'll come up to because it's like I probably like had searched for them so much that I'm associated with them
And then where's Paige you just met her and she disappeared well Paige is probably doing readings on her channel a lot
She is I'm you know Alexander started attacking her and said
That she was a man and stuff and you know, so I don't know if she wants to come run my channel right now
Um, but yeah, she said that she was like trying to like lure men to my channel to like so she could like legally extort
I mean, it's like she's trying to make people scared to come here. I mean, it's like, I mean, I mean, she's like
None of these things will happen to you on my channel. You know, I can't I can't even get a police report file about him
My life is threatened and stuff. So
Josie is hiding after old man trying to look up, oh yeah, yeah, oh yeah, an old man at good times
Good times I got her last name
Well, I mean, it's like, you know, I knew her last name too, but I mean, it's like, you know, I didn't like
I mean and she friended me on Facebook. See that's how I'm special I'm special, you know
It was a good time. Well, good times had her Instagram, but then he found her last name on Instagram
And so he so he added her on Facebook using that last name and people thought it was kind of weird beep
No, no, no devilized made a video, but I can't find devilized in the videos. It's devilized his channel gone
I know there was one of me. That's not very flattering, but
Yeah, God body and you want to see God body you want to see like
Something bad. Let me see if I know if you're still here. I can play the beat of the beat of fight. That was terrible
It was just like so sit some terrible. Wait, what's up? What's up? God body says, uh
She's scaring people. Yeah
well
Yeah, I mean
Some of these women are scaring me now. I mean, but up here I'll show you this fight
I had on a show where some of my neighbor actually broke my window
Cause he was like, he was like so mad, you know, um, you see, it's calls at my right
account.
It's this, yeah, I got it.
Okay.
So yeah, this was what happened with beta one night and I was on this like third channel
trying to like, you know, it's like lay low and stuff here.
Okay.
Not now.
Let me get to my channel.
You'll like this though.
But BBB like a parry a parody of this and it's like so insulting. It's like
Not BBB, I mean devil eyes. I was like I was all dirty and be looked all good and stuff
But I'll play the real thing. This is like the real thing that happened
This is on my psyche's nightmare channel has live streams and they only posted on a few times
So it seems I heard a fine. Can you see like a famous one? Yeah, I found it. Okay. Are you see it?
I never broke the window.
And you're like, hey, Tony, oh, let me get you, hold on.
The only time I really like posting out videos
is when I'm like, what's the second?
Making fun of people and people making fun of them.
I don't know if I'm favorite, but yeah,
that's all I really need to do.
Pushing into music and everybody hanging out.
Let's play this.
Okay, one.
Watch what happens.
Put up the.
Background just just is not to offend. It's just to make sure that I have the correct person in the chat
Overlay come on. Where's this one? There you go. Is it overly shit?
Okay, I'll just keep myself open
Wow, it's been a while since you had a guess. What's up, Ricky?
Rookie, I had a guest last night and this morning.
What are you talking about, girl?
What is this garbage you're watching?
I'm watching a police interrogation about the social media.
But what?
What do you think you're affecting like a vigilante all of a sudden?
No, it's I have a, you know, I like true crime.
What's your problem?
Everybody likes true crime, but how many questions?
Why'd you go up on reality, Nancy, by the way?
Like, you know, up for no reason.
Are you spazzing out, gay fuck?
Are you spazzing out, bitch?
Your mom was spaz out when she fucking gave birth to you.
Fuck you, bitch. I mean, what's your problem?
Why are you bringing up Raleigh Nancy, whore?
Because we're doing Christmas.
I'll treat you so fucking bad, you fucking petal supporter.
Oh, shit. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
The L.D. was on your show after mine. Okay, right? Right?
After mine?
Yeah, after mine.
No, he wasn't.
Can you prove that? $100 bet?
$100. Even $5.
$5 bet.
You're cheap. You can't even afford a McDonald's.
$5 bet $5 bet $5 bet
Are you scared $5 bet LD was on my panel after yours
Do you can you pay can you pay me $5 for your life?
Can you tell me about my life?
You just literally said that LD was on my panel after yours. So can you pay me $5? No, I'm not gonna be
Because you can't afford it, right?
Hey, we were doing section 8 housing in a few years ago Karen told me everything. Can you prove that too?
Well Karen knows. If there's section 8 housing in Orange County for women under, you know, age of 64
You know you're fucking wrong because you're 63, right? Is your mom part of the, you know, housing?
Illuminati? Yeah, she is.
He must have because she gave birth to you you're a weirdo. I have a weirdo. You're a total fucking weirdo. I'm a creep
I'm sorry. Guess what? I always told you this psyche. You
You can even take a little feather from my fucking life. You will be okay, but you're sorry. What are you gonna kick me? You're sorry
What what what are you what bitch you never got on like that?
You're sorry ass motherfucker. Sorry ass bitch
Since you had a guess on your panel let alone me I win this morning
What? Who was it?
Who was it this morning? Okay, we'll-
Aw, so let me put it in my journal.
Let me just write it down, cause I'm Vita. I'm Vita.
Aw, because I'm fucking stupid and psyche, and I know how to determine and fucking read cards.
My ass. Read this asshole.
Read this asshole, bitch!
Read my asshole!
You're a fucking foolish step four.
I've seen it. You should have your blogger and everything.
I'm gonna be that!
But see that! Oh!
Fair black bush, Vita. We all said Vita.
Fuck you, N-word.
Oh, wow. I'm not really...
Well, you said it all the time, right?
And then you said, N-I-G-G. You spell it out, right?
I know. I will, because, well, you are N-word.
And you are too, but you're white, except I'm a Santa in words.
Yeah, you're a Santa.
Well, not in tricks.
What is tricks back?
No, tricks didn't come back.
But you know who came back?
His tux came back.
He came back right up to tricks.
So he came back up for you.
That's ironic how you switch a roux.
I did this little switch.
It's like, Alcliffe.
I'm going to take off, you know, the cute little shagaroo from tux,
and I'm going to put a tuxedo on.
Shut the fuck up, poor face.
Or fucking faith you degenerate as
Stooges, okay, lady. I saw your like bald spot your fucking real face. Yes. I've seen everything now and I showed everybody else
We all know I'm so crushed by your opinion. That's what you saw
Listen, we've seen your balls, but we've seen your who files fucking is my ball
Your leg we've seen your shoplifting out of
I look better than every fucking generation combined together you
been fucked by the Persian spell. I'm Persian. I have good genes. You're a fucking white trash.
White trash on math. Oh, you're white trash. Look at your teeth. They're so yellow.
Just like your vagina lips, right? Why are you doing your hair like that? Like,
you can't compete. Like, you want me to braid it? What?
Oh, it's like the whole chat is like nails on chalkboard you see me and guess what you would have had an opportunity to see me more
But guess what? I'm Persian. You're still like
Garbage your garbage fucking garbage bitch
You can't right because i'm a treasure in your fucking world. I dare you
throw me out garbage garbage. This is the best content you've
had in fucking weeks, whore out of the face.
Oh, okay. All right. You were dropped on the fucking head.
That's why you fucking associate with yourself like camey's Cowboys that you knock about with me
Right talk about control, right?
Who cares about fucking reality, Nancy?
Reality, Nancy?
Like, let her show her fucking shit and we'll laugh about it.
You're just a hater, bitch.
You're just a hater.
Are you jealous?
You're a bad named Q supporter, if I get.
Oh, my God.
You're a Q supporter.
You support Q.
What am I? I'm Brandon Q. You smoke Q.
You spit on a woman.
What, you had her?
You're a faggot that Brandon supports like a faggot Q in the whole.
You're a bitch, wet brain, white claw addict.
You're braiding your hair trying to compete with me right now.
Oh yeah, I want to look like you.
If I had no hair.
Do you want to wear my skin?
You have a bald spot, bitch.
Okay.
And you do too.
And you're a fucking 46 years old looking like fucking a method like a whole lot of good times.
But I never met you because you used to look good at one time, but you look like a whole lot of fucking math.
I wouldn't sit with you at a fucking restaurant in Rosaldo Beach Home. You look like trash. You look like trash. You look like a homeless ass trash bag.
Yeah. Yes, yes.
I reject fucking Elisa Giordano.
You think I would reject trash like you?
I thought you were above that.
You were trash.
You're trash.
You don't know how to fucking like,
you don't even know how to fucking take care
of your fucking trash.
Show me fucking tricks.
Show me tricks.
Rigs ran away.
I will fucking, I will put a fucking knife in my,
I'll put a knife in my,
put a knife in my skull if you show me tricks well i love it show me show me tricks and i'll
do it for you i'll do it no no i'll do it show me tricks you motherfucker you piece of shit
you fucking let your cats get caught you leave your cats locked in the house oh really i'd rather
have them here they're not there i'd rather have them
fucking not having flea and fucking bringing out rats oh yeah i do yeah you keep recycling your
fucking trash ass white fucking trash ass motherfucker yeah okay good luck
As many as your mother has oh my my mother doesn't drink white Claw
She's much more classy than if she was taking it a little bit of sips up when she fucking gave birth to you and she
You can talk about anything
leave her alone. I'm going to go right hard on her. Oh really? I will defend you. I will
defend you. You want to see all the garbage she said about you? I'm Sifa. You're not allowed to
say the word effort on this panel.
Go ahead, Vida. You remember when I was an admin for you, talk about control, get control
off the ass by Brandon Q and pedal supporters. I'm here to fucking entertain your fucking
pedal ass motherfucker. Fuck you and everybody that gave birth to you. You're trash. You're trash.
You're trash. No, you are bitch. You're trash.
Where's Jamie's cowboy settlement in the trash, right?
Oh my god, boy, that's coming in.
Where's her fucking, where's her trash-out settlement?
Oh, yeah, he's fucking Mimi.
Oh, he's got, he's got, he's got, he's got Ho-Ho-Tol.
You look like a rat.
Whoa.
He'd rather fuck Mimi than Europe.
I'll fucking, fucking kangaroo box you all night long, bitch.
Good.
I can fucking beat you.
I'm not kidding you, Root, too.
Come on, bitch.
Ready?
Mimi, halfway.
I'll meet you halfway
Meet me halfway, I swear to god I fucking bitched off you whore
Oh my god
Meet me halfway, but I'm not going to fucking redondo but you're sorry
Again
Yeah, what's your thing with the thing
Hopefully I'll find trick on the way when I come there
I'm sure, but no, no, I guess Tony already, Tony your best friend already has him, right?
And Jamie is your best friend right the cycle path that fucking supported Katie's like Katie's fucking sorry
Listen, I have a new product. It's called Psyche's Bud Pluck Nightmare. Do you want to buy one?
Beat his bush. Beat his black bush.
Oh, really? What are you going to make it out of your fucking Saria beard?
I'm not Karen's video.
What are you going to make it out of? What are you going to make it out of?
You're disgusting.
Okay. All right. Okay. Stop stealing my ideas, Thor.
No, you and Saman look like Chrissy the Clown.
I didn't get down to Osama. Nobody brought Osama.
Nobody brought up yelling Nancy hair is yours. Yeah. Not
everybody can have a no eyebrows like, like, you know,
people have no eyebrows. My eyebrows are perfect. They're on
fleek, bitch. Okay,
they look scary.
Oh my god, you just see you when you look like three more from the three Stooges. How about everybody in your family?
It looks like a cow woman. Oh my god. Well, you look like a rat. I mean, please
I never heard that one before you look like a rat
How do your vagina smell beta welcome to my world bitch
Show me your fucking tattoo show me your tattoo. Yeah, how about this buck BKG?
How about that versus fuck that this isn't the fuck didn't hurt when you got BKG and everything and you just the fuck hurt less, right?
Nothing hurts nothing because I'm a man. I can take everything first every time you take a shower
Every time you wake up every time you change your nasty-ass fucking shirt every time you're
Fucking see that tattoo is you're gonna think of me
You're gonna think of me
BKG be those kiddies for fucking life
Our groomer gang barian cater groomer gang. That's what it sounds for and it says fuck them, right?
I'm a groomer now.
No, I said Barry Kate, not Bita.
I don't care if it's negative energy.
BKG is negative energy, black RG.
You don't get it?
You dumb fuck.
Fuck RG, come off here please,
because I'm not getting this.
I'm not getting where I'm being called a groomer now.
So I don't think I want to have them up.
Fuck you, why not?
Because you're scared of fucking anybody
that has to challenge you.
You're a bummer on your show.
Well, I'm going to fucking leave too,
because that's what you're ice-lidding your life.
I'm just talking to you.
No, fuck you.
I'll go live, and you know what? You can come off there.
I try to give you a little bit of view of your piece of shit, pedophilic.
You support pedophiles!
Oh, you're a boy for the pedophile.
Sam ends up fucking pedophiles.
My boyfriend is a pedophile. You're fucking disgusting.
Oh my god, he gets like, gets care and saw everything.
I didn't know my boyfriend was brown and cute.
That's your boyfriend.
Let fucking RG up here for face.
Let him up here.
Yeah.
Sam, man.
Let him up here.
He's not even trying to get up.
So I'm not gonna open the panel.
Fucking crack face up.
You open it up.
Open it up, Meped.
Open it up.
Open that whole ass up, bitch.
Let's open it up.
Let's look at what your mom looks like.
Let's see how many fucking, uh, like, uh, like searches she's been under.
And you too you're gonna talk about my nose you hide in the background in the dark
That's the only thing that you can
You see that she's got she won't show her face and she's got skin tags and
stuff around her eye, this came on by accident, your chair listening to Karen is listening to your
fucking asses, fucking idiot, imagine listening to Karen, I'm still waiting here, imagine, imagine.
I was always thin when I was a kid too, it's only at that time that I'd gotten fat.
And it was only for like two and a half years.
That one time she got fucked.
And I'm full of seeing me, but look at this ugly mug.
She can't change this.
One thing I won't do is shame fucking people in the look.
And her nose is just as big.
I'm not gonna shame your looks, but is that what you look like?
You keep doing that, and that's what you think
I want you to look like.
You won't show face.
That's what you think what's I'm gonna look like.
And you're gonna retell others.
There is a beautiful face, natural face.
And Bita said that too.
You know, Crystal, Maria even went on camera show face and Vita still did a show face.
Have you seen iron? That's an empty fish tank in the back, and the air mattress is below that. It's a green mattress. He's gorgeous. He lives in section eight.
He has no job.
He's in prison when he was 16, and yes, he did get great.
Well, let me tell you something. When you're almost getting to a waka noodle, I'm going to mute myself and then we can talk.
a few times in there
This is him when you're ready. Show face
I'm gonna read your card right now KK had showed all this because they used to FaceTime see this
I don't know if he didn't, I don't think he did it on purpose, but he's not going to listen to us drink it in the lean, the bowl down.
Hey, what's up, everybody? Thank you for being here. You like that? I mean, it's like, I have a little bit more of it. I mean, it's like, but it's like, um, yeah, hold on a second.
I mean, it's just, it went all bad.
It's kind of depressing to watch that I mean that's when they right then is like when the guy like comes at my door
And he starts being in the door you can kind of see me get up and then he like smashes my window right after that
I'll show you
Oh, shit. Okay, hold on. Let me see you make him a history. Yeah, it goes on for a little longer here
I mean, yeah, but they look like literal monsters. I mean, it's like so crazy
I better hear the hurt. Yeah, I think so that's not her right there. That's that's another person. But yeah
Now, let's do a reading. I'm gonna do a reading for you. I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna do it for you, bitch.
All right, all right. Well, it was more interesting than parent talking. All right, it's Peonies. Peonies. Peonies.
What are they?
Have a rage attack or how about you have a flying hernia? Who cares? Oh, okay. Is it?
motor raffle. Wow. It means that you swear on your fucking forehead on someone's life. You actually, you got a tattoo, most of me stamped, but for me is loyalty. If you think I'm lying, you guys Google that shit. I swear to God, I just call, I just pulled it out. It means the stamp of loyalty. When somebody gets a tattoo of you and they said,
That's it. I'm now going to read the rest. And I don't need AI for that fucking shit.
How Fizz would lower himself to read that? That's disrespectful to the profit.
And you lower yourself to a bunch of fucking cuddles, but that's okay. Okay, let's talk about that.
Fizz, there's better than you as a...
Oh, yeah. All right. Listen, have I ever posted pictures of you?
I'm going to start because you just did.
Oh, I just did? What? That's your picture?
Do it again
You can do it all night long, but you know what I don't do
If I don't fucking fuck around with the fucking high layer higher above your dad wouldn't want you to do that to other females
My mom wouldn't want me to do that to you. Have you ever seen me do that people will do picture change. I don't do that to you
Your mama fucked up when she got plastic surgery. She looked like a fucking cat woman
No, I'll read I'll read the poetry really quickly voice my neighbors broken my window. Okay, so
I'm so glad every time I join your panel. You fucking have somebody trying to fucking get a police call on you
He do you miss tricks ever cuz I miss
So much
Oh, very much how much tell me because if I can get one night with mom at Ali
Because he does he once in a while. He wants to sleep with me keep I would go crazy
I'll be fucking in world in the street like a cowlady
What are you doing on panels like well, you should be looking for tricks. Oh, I should be out 24-7, right?
Yeah, you should be instead of stealing out fucking coffees, right?
Mm-hmm coffee bitch. I went I feel what was that? What'd you steal? I didn't steal anything
But you can talk about my fucking look what you don't never fucking ever get near
With a 10-foot fucking pole, but I will tell you exactly how you are trash
You could have had already met me like you met Alex and Alex is good
He's beautiful
And guess what? We're all individually, like, beautiful in different ways.
And you would've, like, met me and you would've been like,
I fucking got to know this fucking stupid bitch Persian fucking psycho.
But what? You're never gonna fucking meet me.
But guess what? BKG is fucking tattooed on your heart.
On your fucking heart.
It's as fucked BKG, bitch.
And you did not two years later
Oh, how did you fucking cope for two years?
Crash out mother fucker
Chad eating grad fucking flee from the fucking piece of shit
Hey cunt. Hey cunt. You're just a cunt and you know, you can go die. Okay. I can't
Really can't why can't you?
Because I'm a cunt.
Well, anyway, you know, so you're just a fucking joy to be around, you know, it's like...
I'm just a biscuits and I'm gonna fucking suck your biscuits gonna be sucked.
I'm gonna suck your biscuits dry as a bone lady, and you're still fucking thirsty for it in the desert
So fucking thirsty
Fuck you and your fucking thirsty add dry cotton mouth a bitch. Okay, right? Okay
Okay, okay
Rodano asked beach as motherfucker. No gas fucking person wants to fuck you in a whole LA
Everything your fucking profile. They see your picture. They just see Jeffrey Dahmer. I try to hook you up with a like decent
I'm like, you're just a fucking weirdo. Yeah, he was handsome. So what?
Who was the guy that GP GP do?
Well, we're handsome to your boyfriend. I
Was with him for eight years. What happened to your boyfriend?
What happened to your boy?
That's exactly what happened.
It was like fucking quitter.
It was like a quitter.
You just burped it through like your fucking asshole.
You probably fucked him up.
You just let him fucking like downward fuck you,
and you're fucking queued out of your asshole.
That's what happened.
Yeah.
Eight years.
He was your boyfriend, right?
Your kid, your colleagues, has been very cappinets, right?
Do you have any proof?
Well, you said, oh, you'll never prove it. So I can't but it's like you will prove it man
We can't prove it then you're fucked
Why would you fucking like why would you fucking not have any proof?
No, I just know from your voice. This is my how do you know? Are you a voice detector now? Cause I thought you were a psychic
I am fucking gay. I am fucking psyche. I have fucking thoughts in your face. What do you expect from me?
What do you know? What do you know about fucking voice detection? What is your problem? Why do you sound like a man?
Because I fucking think that you like man. I need to be the perfect AI for you. Should I bent over?
Should I go over to the couch? What do you want me to do?
So I keep do you want me to kill a chat for you?
Is that what you want me to do? Fuck you motherfucker.
I'm not killing cats. Are you? That's what you like to do.
You're not insane. What happened to trick? What happened to trick? What happened to tricks?
We're trying to wait because cats sometimes run away. That's just for tricks. That's just for tricks. That's just for tricks.
Tristan's fine. Don't let him out. There's too many Bobcats. There's too many fucking coyotes. Wow
How many times will you tell you? How many times?
From magic
Right
Shut the fuck up, you fucking whoreface, as irresponsible, no fucking, like, I hate you.
I hate you.
I know you do, but it's okay.
I know, I do.
I hate you.
I hear that you do.
You love me.
I hate you.
Remember when you wanted to cuddle with me?
Fuck no, not anymore.
That takes now used to be actually decent used to be like a clean ass motherfucker
You let this fucking internet turn you into a fucking trash bag. Fuck you
I wouldn't touch you with a 10 foot tall.
I let it remain to a trash bag.
Bita, look at yourself in the mirror, okay?
Ms. Projector.
Really?
I don't fucking have my cap dragging in there.
You've seen my face in the mirror?
Yeah, have I been over to your-
Have you seen my face in the mirror?
No, you come, yeah.
You lick my fucking face if you saw in the mirror.
And my ass combined together.
You got a tattoo of my fucking name on your chest.
Because fuck you on it.
I have BKG on your heart.
Oh my god, you were crazy.
BKG, on your heart.
And you were so scorned you had to put a fuck above it.
Yeah, you're crazy.
Explain that.
You know, you've gone insane.
Like, you really have crossed the line.
I mean, it's like, you really, it's like everyone in the chat is like,
wow, they cannot believe it.
Even your chat was against you tonight.
Your chat is ridiculous, and there are a bunch of us.
Big suckers.
That quote is simple.
It's your best friends.
And they're like, you're a doctor.
Ben Paulus says I'm a doctor.
Then pause are you supporting psyche and Brandon too now?
That's all I need to know. Yes or no. Yes
Let me hear your pulse
We have the big fat bitch sleepy. Oh
But you're fat as big as fucking fucking face
Called fucking ghost that you fucking jerk off to every day
No, he drinks off some meat, but you know what?
You're still disgusting.
You're kicking off some meat.
You need a call.
Wait, did I have sex for you?
Eda has my suit.
Oh, my God, Eda.
Oh, my God, this is so embarrassing for you.
I'm so sorry.
Like, how much did you drink?
I'm embarrassing, but Korean people had to fucking go,
I'm talking about you!
You drank way too much you guys you guys psyche stole out of the Korean as fucking economy you guys
First so I so you're saying I asked for the cigar which they had what happened that it was a cigar
Yes, it was a cigar. It was a $2. Okay. Okay for it. Oh
Why are you over a dollar? Why why the convenient fucking nearest or a dollar?
A dollar, I'll throw a dollar and I'll aim it at your white-ass asshole.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
I would do that on-
They smile in your face while planning your fall
But the jokes on them now are already red at all
It's run by those who see the design, they lie, they manipulate, they play
But I learned the game yesterday
Never fight with your innocence
Draw no fuel, cyclist today
I see the game, I see the game
Shing for cracks
Givelly said something that changed everything
The wise man said once what the fool does
Finally, translation
I'm already finished while you're still starting
Foregone conclusion, you can promise to let you break
And comprehend what you can
Can't begin what I've already penned
See, isn't defeating your inner
By the way, if you're gonna steal it fucking do thousands you don't know for a dollar, right?
I would do that on a shoe for a dollar unless it was a dollar
You stole for a dollar I didn't steal the thing. He did I didn't but yes, you did you were walking out and he said
It's a beautiful day and you got your ass
I sold coffee. Oh, I sold coffee because there's free refills for coffee. So I stole it, right?
Free refills every day. Free refills every day, but now I pay for it once a day and then I get free refills.
Why don't you get a coffee maker? Why don't I get a coffee maker? Why don't I need a beta maker?
How about that?
Because I'm not your fucking slave. I didn't say you get it for me. I said a coffee maker.
Or what are you saying? You're a coffee maker because you make coffee?
Okay, I'm not gonna make shit for you fucking whore-ass fucking bitch. You remember this? You remember this beta?
I'm saying to show you what you're gonna play more fucking stupid AI shed or like
picture picture you think it's gonna face me
oh I'm so faced by your fucking dislike I would do a mercy killing
I'm not a religious person. I don't even believe in God. I don't I don't even believe in God fucks
Just I will mercy kill you. I would do killing
Bullshit in his fucking life
That's you
Thank you
I'll bitch slap you like before that you are
I'm making fucking slime right into the wall.
Norted.
Stunning.
Bye.
See you later.
Hey, hey.
Elia.
Shout out to Tripp and K.
Thank you.
W.
We always win.
But don't jump to conclusions.
W.
This iconic arachnid is mostly misunderstood.
She's not a bad girl.
She just looks like one.
This is the Black Widow.
Black widows are a type of spider perhaps best known for...
I killed one today, bitch!
This whole cannibalism...
I would kill a black...
I would kill a black spider on a daily.
She has a sweet side, right?
that it's like the mean side is
I thought of exes or something and she's like, she's like, yeah, one of them is murdered.
Yeah, you look like a tard.
And I do.
I look great.
No, you don't.
You're talking about me.
Of course.
That's great.
How about when you talked to Blondie?
What the fuck would you do, like a semi-documentary about me, your tard?
And I would have been like, great, you're joking.
I had to experience meeting a Black woman.
Why are you antagonizing me?
Exactly.
Why do we know Christine?
Why isn't Christine over there in your chat?
Is because me?
I'm telling Christine.
Do you guys want to run?
Come on.
You should have.
Fucking paranoid.
Hell yeah.
He went on a round page trying to follow a bunch of people.
Yeah.
My thought was, yo, like he, yo, I don't know.
All of a sudden he's following me.
What a desperate, desperate.
Yeah.
Nancy, are you still speaking like Alaska first?
Alaska first behavior.
I don't know we're gonna get Emma. We're gonna get Emma. Oh, yeah, we're gonna get Emma.
We're fucking Amber and Alicia. I'll make sure to get that open in my stage. You can do it in your stage too.
I don't give a shit I'm not ever come around like accusing people of like
Really really really outrageous behavior. I love long day. What's up? Yeah, you won't what a man
Especially when I got the chinching and the ding-a-ling wasn't it? I don't want to take your inheritance that you got it from the thrift store
Well, I don't want to take your inheritance. I want you to travel around and enjoy that while you can
I've been trying to have a thrifting intermission, but if you had any assets and property sitting solid, like under your fucking
The other one you fucking beg me to take care of your cat, we're fucking defaming you.
Mikey, remember when you messaged me, I will put those up there, that's funny.
Why is that song stuck in my head?
I'm gonna tell you a good person.
I'll do that right now, that'll be hilarious.
It's Troy.
I love the perfect song for it.
This song is not my big size at all.
I have the perfect song for it.
You're a fucking messager.
Let's do it right now.
You should shut their fucking mouth about it.
You need to listen to it.
It seems like you do.
A ticket.
You need to listen to it.
I paid on time.
Really?
All of that.
I have no criminal records.
No restraints working with me.
And like January, I don't
But guess what you do
You
i don't talk shit i love blogger what's the protection by i love blogger i kiss him right
on the left i know he's gonna fucking like have any case against me for training people
what the fuck framing them putting them out there i don't know betta listen stop with all the drama
for one minute and let's have a planter intense betta listen listen let's have let's have a drink
I never had a restraining order against me if you had one against you
Double down. Let's see what's gonna actually I got I got drunken through some shit through my ex's window. Yeah
Yeah
You're on credit.
Talking about Arizona.
It was nice talking to you.
I'm going to go live one year right now.
I'm going to go live.
Double down.
It was not nice.
You know?
And guess what?
Guess what, Psyche?
You cannot focus at all.
You're gonna be awake all night thinking about me. It's called a persian fucking persuasion
Gonna be all about you
We're gonna fucking play all the sweet
Witching which game you're in a witch game. Okay broom game, right? You're in a broom game, right? Oh, yeah, I'm in the broom game
We're gonna broom it. Okay, it's probably up your vagina
your whore. Whoa, reality you heard that? That's a salt. That's a lot of salt. That's a lot. That's a lot.
Reality call put that I'll be right back. Okay, bye. Wow.
Okay guys, so while I was talking to her,
kind of yelling and stuff like that,
my neighbor, who doesn't like me,
came and started kicking my door.
And I went down and I was like,
why are you kicking my door?
And he said, oh, you're being loud or whatever.
It's 9.30 in the night, by the way.
It's not even 10 p.m.
And then I closed the door and then he broke my window.
So what should I do?
What should I do?
What do you think?
Oh my gosh, look at that web brain in the chat now.
I can't believe she can type.
She must have a voice activated thing.
So what should I do?
Should I call the police?
Or should I call the owner of the property?
Yeah, let's see, Bita, let's just see.
Your loud voice got my neighbor to like break my window
and he's probably gonna be a victim now.
So what should I do guys though?
Oh, and Nancy, you go ahead and ban whoever you want, okay?
I trust my mods, they're better mods than Bita has.
What should I do?
My neighbor broke my second store window. He put me through something through it. Should I call the police or should I call the owner of the building?
Yeah, and be that I didn't see one person on your side in the chat and it's like in boy. Have you like burned some bridges?
I mean, it's like talking about me burning bridges. I mean, it's like whatever you think about, you know, branding here or whatever
You know, branding here is like really like not even relevant. It's like to the situation just now just now Nancy just now
I mean, it was like a few minutes. It was while I was talking to be that when I went downstairs and stuff call the police
My I'll just say that my family owns this property and so there are tenants
So should I call the family first or should I call the police?
I'm just wondering
Because her loud-ass boy is getting me all baby. Yeah, I just had the front door open
But it's like it's not even like I'm just like louder than usual. Yeah, I was kind of loud
They could have just knocked on the door. Should I call the police? I know who did it
He's there's a camera outside plus. I know he was right outside the door when he when I know so yes
Take pictures first. Okay
Okay, I'll go take a picture of the windows into my sister
Okay, I let her know so I might get a call on a minute or something like that. Yeah, I have the I have the picture of it here
Here's the broke my window. Yeah, there's cameras. There's cameras outside. I hope I hope it's on so
They texted her about it
He could have like, you know, if I'm being loud and you say, can you please be quiet and I want to shut the door
Shut the window and everything. No, he comes kicking my kicking my door when she's on when I'm all with her and then he
Broke my window. You'd have to break my window. That was crazy
You see it's like I just don't like it because I have the you know, I cats around and stuff like that
But I let her know I see a fucking bitch named Bita
You're gay
Wow, yeah, how long have we been in love with Katie Beaver?
Call me Crip, no, six, seven.
OK, what are you doing?
I'm making a video.
Yo, I'm making a video for my mom.
You want to say hi?
No?
He waved, he waved.
I was on wave.
Look, Psyche, look, it's Psyche backing up into his house.
That's not me.
That Psyche, look, you're walking backwards right now.
Into your house.
That's I'm a truck. All right, should I press all those switches? Yeah
Thank I'm gonna I'm gonna do it. He told I'm gonna do like up down left. I'm talking to him in the car
I ain't
Now he's not a Crip. He's Latin King. Okay. I can't talk to him
Like this guy can't talk to me because
There's somebody that's a guest and it does and outside your window. I am scary picture
I'm out of here
Okay, you say hi to my mom. I'm making a video
You say hi to my mom. Thank you
I still was like freaked out like bro like what the fuck can't I do can't say hi to my mom
What?
I'm in new york. Say hi to my mom. Hello
Bang
Hello
That guy was yeah that guy was like what the fuck what's wrong with this guy
We're all here being real quick members.
So when's this threatened to grate me?
I'll do that just for fun.
Oh, shit, what is this?
So you have like a following on my channel.
Yeah, what do you mean?
Of course I do.
They're like, bang.
Of course I do, what is this, a timing belt?
Yes, yes, woohoo, they're like,
they're like, they're doing smiley movies.
That old man was scared of you, it says.
So it's sort of a timing belt.
They're like, bang.
Hey, hey say
You should like say I'll you choose cool new catchphrases to use say
Slither slither and just a slither all the time and then say spook spook and then my phrase my catchphrase
My sleeper you want to know what my sleeper agent phrases?
My sleeper agent activation phrase
Wait, this is MKUltra, I'm sensitive to this concept.
Yo, I used to come out here and shoot up meth into my veins.
Oh my gosh, you did?
Yeah.
When was this?
Like a real savage.
What the fuck?
Somebody said, I'm outside your window, get ready.
I'm going to come in you.
That's crazy.
Yeah, but that's not you writing that?
No, that's not me, no.
That guy was looking at me like I was insane.
He's right. Let's see if we can find crack vials and used condoms. So there's needles. So you go
That's from yesterday I was using that oh my god
$10 $10 donation to my cash up and I'll jump into traffic from here
Yeah
Okay, you know you jump in the traffic. I don't know. That would be like a
That's the George Washington Bridge. It is and I'm not in New Jersey
Across the water
You're in California. I miss Crip. You're crippled. You're you're um, you're handicapped person. Okay
Well, that's that's not surprise. You have to go lobster claw for a hand
Yeah, he only does he has a good hand is like it's like suck like this. I can't as I'm not trying to do it on purpose
I see you, huh? That's all that's probably like that Los Angeles overpass or something. Those rotted limes. Oh
Free lunch. Oh
They're like rotted. No, they're rotted limes. I think it's like I think it's like excrement. Oh, I could use the different lenses on this
Oh shit, okay
We will is that the way the Vincent Thomas bridge. No, this is the George Washington bridge
Yes, it is. What are you talking about? It literally is I can show you the sign. It's over there where you're in Washington
No, this is Harlem
Harlem in New York. Yes, this is Harlem. No, you're from like you're from California, aren't you?
I'm from where all the black people live
My family actually founded Harlem
Let me see how many meth heads I could find if I go through here. I'm gonna shoot up meths. I know psyche knows all about that
You know what I know, I know you have a small wiener. Can you show me to me bad? I have a transformers
My penis transforms into a vagina
Bang, this is not upstate New York Harlem is not in upstate New York. That's crazy
Yeah, well, it's been found by Dutch people like my ancestors
Yeah, look that's psyche on his motorcycle
Looking for gay guys to have
New York City is so much more like crowded and dirty
This is LA LA is beautiful. I'm from LA where all the black people are
You're in a forest
Hey, if you've got a New York City has a lot of parks
What do you mean? And if you've got a house made of candy would you start eating it?
And if there was a wish that lived there, would you move in?
Let her feed you. I don't know. I don't think so
Doesn't sound like a great idea for gingerbread and her name is beta. Oh
Well, if it's beta, okay
But what if she ate you she could eat me all she wants
They literally ate you like you know cannibalism. Hello
Call me grip. No
All right, there's no gate here. So I'm gonna have to just jump over this
It's okay since I'm eight feet tall. I could just walk over this
Looking for a gay
I'm over here right here. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. I
Forgot where I parked
He looks like a woman from like Scooby-Doo with Down syndrome.
What is her name?
Scooby-Doo, where are you?
He looks like Belm with Down syndrome.
Oh my God.
He's definitely not a Cripp, God buddy.
He's three up to C.
I'm gonna call me Cripp, you know, 67.
He's not even just disabled.
I think that's all he can do with his hands.
There's my car right now.
Where's my car?
If he says, yeah, he looks like Shaggy with the downsides.
Dude, where's my card?
Yeah, you look like all the entire Scooby-Doo
cast with Down syndrome.
Should put them all together, including Scooby.
Is this where you're going to shoot up meth?
You can't show that OK.
It's too sad.
I just remembered I have a can of soda in my car.
Let me go get him.
It looks like you have a bunch of pubic hair glued to your face, what's wrong with you?
What is that on your chin?
I'm gonna steal from my car.
He doesn't, everyone's saying he looks gay
and he looks like he's wearing lipstick.
And he keeps getting mad and like,
I'm gonna kick him off and stuff.
Back.
Is he wearing lipstick?
Hey.
Yo.
Hey, are you, does the three in a glow wear lipstick?
Oh yes, I can confirm this.
Why does he wear lipstick?
Because he's gay?
Is he ever kissing you?
Gay guy.
When he kisses you, does he get the people who stick on you, and do people think we work as the young woman?
Because he's a gay guy.
How does it feel to look like that when you look at the mirror? What do you really think?
I don't really look at myself in the mirror.
You don't ever put your wiener between your legs and pretend you have a vagina?
So, no, I've never done that before, man.
And I turn around and, like, poke it through the other side.
Maybe I should consider doing that.
So, it's interesting.
It's interesting.
Ooh, we have a soda.
How hot is it in New York?
Well, guys, I have the weather on my chat.
It's like 100.
What city are you in?
What city in New York are you in?
I can just, like, go, like, what, Alvin?
I'm in Harlem.
I'm in Manhattan.
OK, hold on.
And then I go, Harlem, New York, so it happens.
Okay, many, many, many, many, many, many clouds.
Omens are favorable.
That's cool. You have a you know nightbot could do weather. I know I had to set it up special to do it
But yes, you have to pay for that. Nope. It's free. I just got the weather service API. Oh shit. Okay
Psyched the programmer
Retarded old fart would have figured it out for himself
So what are you, are you working today?
Are you delivering stuff like Grubhub or something?
No, I don't work.
Uber, you're just driving the car around?
I don't work for a living.
I just have other people.
Are you trying to pick up women?
Shit.
Bye.
Trying to pick up women?
Nah, women are trying to pick me up right now.
What, the police?
Is there a female cop around?
So did you ever see Black Eyed Andy get arrested twice
in one day?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
He's lucky as his parents around me. Well, that's lucky, but but then for you to do that
That's just retarded
Yeah, you're right. It's lucky, but that's it's not lucky to be that retarded
Let's find the video where he's that's the way the cookie crumbles chat. Am I right?
That's from the movies from the movie babes in Toiland. That's the way the cookie crumbles chat
Let's see if I can find this blackout Andy clip, chicken Andy, or is it Christine?
Josette, Josette, grassy, craziest people on here usually have the most money it seems like.
Having money shields you from consequences.
If blackout Andy had to stay the whole weekend in jail, if he had to serve whatever time the judge set for him,
Without bail if he didn't have mommy and daddy to pay for that. Do you think he would be doing that?
He wouldn't be doing that because nobody's gonna bail him out and you think blackout Andy's gonna sit there in prison
Money money means you can do
More things and that includes being a fucking worthless
turd
unfortunately
And if he didn't have any money, he wouldn't be dying that tell you that much
I'll sit sorrow, across the sorrow, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night long, I'll see you all night
Am I too close bro? Okay, okay
Are you guys mad? Okay, fine
Okay, bye sidewalk dude. I'm on the sidewalk bro. I guess like you got tired of talking
You're getting talked along with this
This is boring
Blackout MD is the most boring person on I don't see I don't see why anybody watches him
What's his origins story? Why does anybody even care about what he's doing to begin with?
Psyche put me full screen. Let me show you my meth pipe. Oh, I got a meth pipe check it out
Man, why is that guy getting invested? What, he was selling drinks?
See the meth walks?
Oh dude, he had a bottle of Patron.
Uh, he had a bottle of Patron, bro. He must have ran out of the-
Patron.
Well, is that Trident?
Well, it's Trident, the police officer-
He's got a bottle of Patron.
Trident? I don't know.
Oh shit, oh shit, oh shit.
I'm sorry.
I'm fucking firing on my phone.
What the fuck?
Oh shit.
Bastard!
I got myself invested.
I got, I got, I got arrested, but who, who was looking to do something? I wonder. Hmm.
Can you play anything that isn't this or AI videos? Please. She called the cops and told them,
hey, you know, yes, like they're dropping them. Yes, just like Skibbles. My charges are being
Skibbles charges are being dropped so mine
Okay, that's cool. Bye. If you don't like my face why the fuck you here faggot nigga
Fuck out of here. Hello lawyers
Yep, they were fun
Yeah, they look great
on my wrists
Yeah, this is pretty good actually
like
Dude, this shit was like purple
This shit was fucking purple, bro
Yeah, I'm going on tonight guys. Thank you. Stop muting me. I'm gonna go out tonight, and it's gonna be
Stop muting a real print
Then they call the cops. Oh shit. I don't miss Holly
miss Holly
Fuck
Well, I'm only taking these shots miss Holly. Let's drink this beer. I'm gonna take a dab
Then we need to call the chefs on Victoria J. We know it doesn't matter
As long as it's documented cops, I'm going to do anything but as long as the cops didn't do anything with BG or Skibbles
But now I have all this evidence. I can say hey look
You're fucked Victoria J
Yes, I need to file a police report
For like telephone harassment
Yeah, yep, I am
Yo, psyche put me full screen. I'm doing IRL fuck this shit
fuck this game guy
the gay hamster
he's been getting calls and emails
he's been getting calls
threatening me
threatening him
saying bad things are gonna happen
bye
you know stuff of that nature
fucking cops aren't gonna do anything
yep
yep ant g
that's why I'm doing it bud
Other cops gonna drive their fucking police cars fucking to Canada and arrest Victoria J. No
Yeah, I know this guy's retarded
Don't worry about it. No, I dropped the pizza on the ground, bro. I saw it outside my window, bro
Right, it's just in the cop car just looking at my pizza on the ground like fuck almost made it home
I'm outside buying blocks. Is the pizza still detained?
It's it's fucking on Victoria
You're fucked. Yo, thank you. Put me full screen turn this shit off. I'm outside fuck this
I'm really outside. I have breath in my body
Which is not right now. I'm really outside
Moving up
I have breath in my body
It will be on Victoria J. No, yo, can you say hi to my stream? What's up?
All right, I know my body
Not right now
The bitch was like nah, why are you Jay had a hand in this bang?
I'm gonna walk in the traffic like blogger
fine, I
Would rather see outside with this guy see what I'm saying. I will you you would rather be
outside with me
back that garbage guy looked at me like I was
I'm fucking
Alright, I survived.
Psyche, turn that shit off!
Nobody gives a fuck!
Turn that shit off, Psyche!
So long as I have breath in my body,
which...
is not...
right now,
as long as I have breath in my body,
it will be on Victoria J.
Not in like a physical way.
But as long as I have breath in my body,
not right now.
Victoria J had a hand in this, bro.
Hey vegan patriot if my dad hates me so much
Hey, psych. Hello, you there. Did you get beat up? No, why?
You're looking up like a prize fighter today
Really?
You're not wearing a shirt. Oh, this is a tree. No, it's way too hot for a shirt. Oh
We have oh, we have another guest back on
I'm smoking mad singing his pipe
I'm in Cancun right now.
You're in Cancun? Oh, how lucky.
Look at it.
This is on vacation.
Have you met any Cancun bees?
Any Cancun what?
Cancun ladies?
Oh, there's plenty here.
I haven't met any, but there's plenty here.
You should hit on them. You look pretty...
Yeah, hit on them. They're all with their
boyfriends or husbands, man.
That's not going to be so easy.
Ah!
Yeah, maybe it's for you
It's way too hot to do anything right now I I was in the pool all morning
Just had lunch had a few drinks, and I'm just I might nap right now
We're shorts
Booty shorts
They dolphin shorts like Richard Simmons wears. No, just like khaki shorts. Okay, because they're filled with poop bang
No, I said they're khaki shorts because they're filled with poop like
Bang
Why don't they sell why don't they sell pre-rolls, but instead of a pre-roll it's like this
That would be a good idea
Why?
Can you hear why are you why are you trying to talk shit about my business plan? I just asked why
Fuck man. We're buzzkill dude. You're buzzkill. What's the fuck up? I'm trying to become a billionaire
shit
Is there a sauna with other men you've been in I try to go I went to the Dollar Tree for lighters. They only had this one I
Was gonna get if I was gonna get a normal lighter, but
I mean, did he have sex? He looks like he looks like so relaxed. I mean, do you have sex with or something like that?
Maybe, maybe not, but no.
He was having sex with himself. Thanks.
Do you have any fruity drinks?
I had margaritas. I had tequila shots and margaritas, and right now I'm having an espresso, and if that doesn't wake me up, I'm gonna go nap.
I saw the headline I saw the title of the stream. What's going on there?
Wow, it's not surprising it was expected she does that she flip flops
More than crystal and I don't feel like I'm dealing with like fish or something like that, right?
Right to forget about a man get on with things don't don't don't obsess over it just get on with things
Can you have your shirt to say hold on
This is really turning gay now. What the fuck?
No, no, this is way too much way too many straight now
Too many naked men now. We're getting straight in here
It is a steam room here, man, it's so hot add like nine o'clock it was already like 30 degrees
It's warm today. It's just warm today. I just imagine we're not even wearing underwear, but it's all in the nude and the sleep.
It's the worst thing you've ever done.
Ben.
Say, we can't see you.
I'm a crib.
Okay, now I feel uncomfortable.
Right? This is weird.
I feel uncomfortable because I'm not wearing a shirt in public and there's a fucking big-ass bee next to me.
There's a bee?
And I'm not wearing a shirt. I know. Maybe that's what the bees like
Trying to get an easy sting
I gotta say this kind of feels nice feeling feeling the radiation on my skin. It feels nice
Yeah, but yeah, but you also weren't born with the
On the CRV. No, you know what you have on CRV
So sorry, I was on the Stephen King's in my speedo and someone said my ball
Dropped out or something. I don't know. I but he got a strike. I'm so sorry. That's disgusting. Are you serious?
That's fucking good. Yeah, you can't stream for a week on that channel. So I'm sorry. That's really gross
That's not good
When was this?
Last night.
Check out all the white bitches with fat ass
Bang, I don't think I think you get a pair. Let's just let's just watch all the white women
Let it close. I think my bulls was too big for the
YouTube, you know, like I think I got a little well
That's what it was right if they were if they were tiny little balls
Nothing would have happened right it would have been like dingleberries or something
that they thought when I was like dancing around and like you're turning around.
You thought you were a female.
That's nasty.
That's very nasty of them.
Stig looks like Stig hit her like that.
There's the crack pipe.
Why do you have it?
Because I smoke crack.
Cool.
Do it then.
Because it's cool.
I'll have it right here.
Slow it up.
Do it.
I'm scared.
Ah!
Of what? I thought you were a crack.
I'm scared to talk about...
I'm scared to talk to the demons
that come out when I smoke meth.
Oh, I see.
You don't like that monkey on your back.
You're talking to me.
Bam.
Let's see. There's somebody coming up here. Hold on.
Bam. Let's talk to this person.
Yo, can you say hi to my stream?
Yo.
Hello, New York lady.
Your bag looks nice.
Okay.
I'm sure you're gonna be very successful this is this is the way to do it. I'm sure
I'm gonna take your lead and do that and I have my crack pipe and my crack lighter. Nice. I
Just need a crack pipe. I just need a crack pipe and I'm gonna do what you do
I'm gonna go around to all the ladies. Hey, will you be in my stream?
My tits are let's have sex on my stream with my titties out
I'm trying to get this rock going that's weed isn't it?
Isn't that just we?
No.
It's big.
I have a surprise preview for you.
I hope you like this.
It's just a preview.
It's not ready yet, but there's just a little preview of what's coming.
Are you ready?
Is it my song?
It will go with your song soon.
But here's the preview I have for you.
Is that supposed to be me?
Why do I look like a pharmacist?
I was looking, I'm going to base it on you now.
You know, I just need a full screen of you real quick.
I'm going to get that picture for you, okay?
I'm going to base it on that.
Yeah, I'm going to make a whole video based on that.
Oh my god, look at SIG.
How's that crack, SIG?
It's good.
Nice.
Looking crack.
Yo, can you say hi to my stream?
Yo, I like your Nike Tech pants.
Then it didn't go through. Yo, can you say hi to my stream?
Where's this fucking ant going?
Where's the fucking end? Oh, shit
Now it's up my pant leg
I've got ants in my pants. I saw a couple rodents before outside my balcony here
I think they're tapers. I'm not sure what they are. Where is he?
Where's beat I want to goon
I'm trying to goon. Where's beat up. I don't know man probably busy
She's probably busy gooning with somebody else that isn't me
Well, that could be
But it does like to goon. Oh, she loves him. That's like that's like top three activities for what are the other two
I can tell you that.
Oh, okay.
Smoky map charts.
Jesus.
This is not working.
Hello, would you like to see...
Would you like to talk to my stream?
Fucking ant.
Sam's gonna fucking kill me.
Oh, shit.
It's coming to me.
Shit, and I'm out of there.
Fucking ants are gonna give me ant aids.
Why am I fullscreen?
adding a picture of
Why is the ball guy full-screen nobody wants to see that right?
They'd rather see your pubic laden chin
You would rather see my super glued beard
chat ten dollars donation and then jump off this
So what what happened with I next like how do you know that she's turned on you? What's happened?
Well, she posted this video basically saying, oh, I'm just a bad person now, and blah, blah, blah.
And she's talked to Alex, and I should leave Alex alone, and blah, blah, blah, blah.
Oh. I see. Yeah. I don't know. She's nuts.
She's nuts. And I'm a squirrel.
You're a squirrel?
Yeah. I'm a squirrel.
Oh shit, Bita overdosed again.
Oh.
Bita overdosed again.
Bita doesn't do drugs.
She only smokes weed, man.
She overdosed again.
On fake mushrooms.
Man, let me finish this math pipe real quick.
Man, I finished this math pipe.
But you said it was a crack pipe.
No, it's a math and crack pipe.
Yeah, both in there. Yeah, I got it's like it's like one of those
Weed pens that has two flavors. I see yeah
But it's not weed is cracking man and the flavors of weed are methane crack
No, no, no, it's actually just the methane crack itself
Why did you look green? It doesn't look green. That's not sort of oh
Shit, there's somebody's you're not supposed you're not allowed to do that in New York. That's illegal
You cannot have an unleashed dogs. New York says Harlem. No, I know you're in New York City
But like what are you doing? Like are you doing something or you just out for a stroll?
I'm out for a stroll right now. Nice
I'm having I'm looking for someone to have sex with aren't we all
W
I posted a short on my page psych of it. I took a little stroll around the resort here. You want to see it?
No, you don't have to show it right now. I'm just saying if you you can look at it
You want to hear that
Okay, yeah, she thinks I'm yeah, I mean
Okay, one second.
Okay, okay, so this is what she posted today.
Okay, hear me stop, so are you ready?
Okay.
Okay, you have to listen to it.
All conversations.
And he's trying to start clap.
I told him to stop, to leave her alone
and sort of going at her about what she happened between them.
And he keeps going on and on and on and screaming at her and he's joining
Panels where he's not even wanted and then they kick him out. He was upset that I guess saying they kicked him out of there
And he doesn't even like salmon. He just goes on there to bitch
And you know psyche. I told you just leave it alone. You're the one obsessed with her and that's why
She's reacting to you. You don't stop
So and then you put on this crazy woman named noelle
And you said, you know her, I don't even know why she wanted to talk to me last week when I was on your panel, because I don't know her.
And you knew, oh, Brandon, it's about the band and she was the acts and she, I don't know her YouTube name in the back backstage or whatever. And I don't even know what that was.
So then she hopped back in on your panel yesterday, I guess.
Or today, I'm not sure because I've been out.
And then all of a sudden you're playing an old video of Alex against me just because you're mad that, you know, just leave her alone and stop making threats to her. You didn't go to any court or anything. And you know that you're really messy.
Brandon because he was trying to take over your your live you said and complaining about your music and then you banned them and everything
No wonder. She's upset with you. You go back and forth back and forth and you keep on just leave it alone
Hey Nancy job. Why don't you get a job?
Because you did ask for money, you know, and I'm not gonna lie about that
So you want me to go ahead and post videos that were more recent about you. You need to get a life
Anyway, this is Kate and everybody's against him right now and they're laughing because
he lost all these people and just going berserk and goes live after live after live making
videos of Alex and then the other day he's sitting there looking all sad, playing some
other videos of her.
You know, maybe just leave things alone and then you're talking about her everywhere you
go.
But anyway, this is Kate calling him out.
a legit predator just talking about brandon i guess he put that's what a good friend does
she wasn't on witski was she what do you need help with ashante it's about psyching that's a good
friend if they like you know if you dig into things a little bit like any beyond the surface level
you'll see what's really going on um with normans to see the truth and i need to clear something up
and have a baby, that's not at all what happened.
I know that what had happened was he was offering
because she wants to have a kid
and sure he has somebody, you know, if she's gonna do it.
And he told her, and we laughed about it,
he told her that he would be willing
to give his, you know, whatever so she can have a child.
but he twisted it yesterday and he was saying that she wanted him to have sex with him.
And that way she gets pregnant and she was shocked. That's a lie, Psyche. She never told you that.
I remember what happened was you offered her, she was talking about wanting to have a kid
sometime and she's still thinking about it, but she never asked you to give her your sperm, your
And her and I spoke twice yesterday. Everything is cool. We have a lot to tell her on IG and
There you are stalking her still you're going on and on about her and you're joining panels
And you got kicked out of three panels. Those are some boobs man lost a lot of people
I mean, you didn't even have many people in your chats, but this is Kate calling you out.
I've got nice really going on.
The truth is, you know, beautiful lies.
Guys, be careful with this guy.
Sometimes the truth is ugly.
Sometimes you'll see, like, how much sled you've been and, like, what's really going on.
They're pretty big, man. He's got pepperoni nips.
Sorry, I don't have beautiful truths for you here.
I have, like, you know, I just have the truth.
The truth is not really pretty right now
I should know the truth is not pretty what's going on
Slander
I can't go in Christine's chat. I can't go. I'm just not welcome in many places and so
I don't know why these people are in my chat and nobody else is, but yeah, just to spread
what's up Brandon?
Oh, just fighting the good fight, you know, again, I'll stand up for truth.
Hey, fighting, you're a weirdo, freaking out, you know.
And, you know, just being harassed by this guy.
Finally.
All these all you can see on the screen with it. 13 minutes in. Oh, I must have been blocked. It's all basically
1327 seconds and he has his first person chat and chat.
Psyche goes with who is drip feeding him money,
currently mayors and Brandon,
he will stand on that hill until-
Can you turn this off?
I can't even fucking near myself.
$85, you know, and-
So INX is reviewing a fake video, I guess.
I also sent him $25.
And then sometimes he's asking for money. It's like, it's about time he get a job. I mean, what's he doing with me?
That's being lucrative. Bingo! Bingo!
We know who it is, but we'll build up again, like, you know, as soon as I can figure out the truth,
I'm sure I'll be the most popular person, right? They are obsessed, right? As soon as they figure
out the truth, he'll be the most popular person. Oh yeah, I don't have to keep anybody's name out of
my mouth. I don't know why. Constantly. Constantly. I'm obsessed. For over a year, he's been sending
Okay, I'm obsessed. He's talking to me and cats and I'm obsessed. Okay, go ahead
He instigated it with beta 2 and then he puts a he made a tattoo of her
YouTube name and something about cats. I love cats or kitties whatever her name is on YouTube and then later he decides to
Think he's gonna get her mad by adding the word f u c k on top of that
Well, why did you even have the tattoo on it look pretty cheap like it was a three dollar tattoo for you?
So he did that. It's like why put that on there. That's ridiculous
You think you're gonna hurt people but you're messy and you jump down all these panels and Kate you are so right about this guy
Now I've opened my eyes to him because he's messy and I told him leave her alone
He's messy and I'm running on and on and on playing videos. No wonder she reacts that as of yesterday
We're fine. You know, I mean and then he's playing an old video from a few days ago
Yes, we were getting into it and she doesn't know anything about my family. We talked last night. She knows more
but, uh, you know, because he even agreed, yes, I know, you know, I take care of myself and me and my siblings are very close, I was one of them, okay, you people don't know that, and we talk all the time, and you really need some support sick, seriously, and we hang out and stuff, so, I mean, this is called gynecomastia surgery, not one single person.
I'll get that done at some point. It's not really a rush about Alex. I don't really care as you can tell alone
Give her time to be wearing a man's ear. Maybe I'm sure she'll do that
You know, I could wear they have compression shirts and then people
About the AI music you keep playing
So let's see what
What else does this person has to say about him? It's Kate
Um, yeah, I mean, it's a YouTube has sort of the demonetizing everybody if they use like thumbnails
Generated by AI if they do anything with and even though YouTube has like all these AI tools that they were
Used they weren't anybody that just started demonetizing them kept their monthly money. They now they're demonetizing for AI thumbnails
But I don't think that's why you're demonetized. They're
Monetized
They're demonetized
Alex has one person in her chat guess who it is Brandon
Well, she did it live about him they busted them
Apparently, yeah, she covered she recapped it live about him being a predator and even called him a predator
It's that live from a couple years ago. Oh my god 2024
of him where I'm on he had vegan state his plays when she was trying to fuck
am I why do we look like Joe Satriani something I don't know you tell me I
don't know I'm wondering I said and everybody that was that if he was
recapping somebody else's recap of that long live and you could see Brandon
practically almost sexually assaulting this woman and vegan was trying to
And he wouldn't leave her alone and they started yelling and had an argument that video is out there because that's the one that I shared on my channel a year ago
No year and a half ago
Shared from KK's
channel
So let's say see what she has to say, but yeah, this guy is messy. It's like get a job, dude
You know Dave. I mean you look like a meth head and everybody's saying you're doing math
Get a job go do live good grass hang out with real people
You were kicked out of that gas station for trying to steal a coffee
I mean, my God, get a job.
I don't know.
What?
Brandon Q showed them DMs that look like it had extremely obvious edits.
Oh, yeah.
It's used.
Oh, God, what's the name of the app?
Yeah, he makes it.
It's an app, Mockly or something like that.
It's an app used to make fake DMs from all types of platforms.
I think it's called Mockly.
We're uh, well, no wonder because he made that's so fucking hilarious
Message to himself saying Alex did it and it was hard to make fake shit because he can't spell right at all
And she was upset and she even posted on her community post that she didn't give him no way a thousand dollars
Then he told us four thousand dollars
Yeah, he's a liar. So he's making stuff up and
Gamble was right. He's got like a
All his bots, those are fake. They're bots. He doesn't have people in his chat
That's why they don't answer anybody and they keep repeating the same thing that he says over and over again
Why is she always late to the party people have been saying this stuff will brain in for a while while she was defending him
And now all of a sudden she's my she's nobody
Thanks, and they're not fake. I can't stand
Call me to kill myself. You know just because I joined
Crystal's panel when they wanted me up there to now all of a sudden when it's convenient for
Now she's repeating
No, I'm not judging you. I'm not judging you try um
Try uh, you know a bath. I don't know
I'm sorry for your discharge
I guess it's like an engine jack all time. So we're saying that it's not
How much is the engine jack pretty frustrating, right? And then that's the engine jack, right?
That's half a ton one couple other channels
Who smokes cigars like cigarettes?
Yeah, he's like eight watchers over. Oh, can you imagine the smell of that apartment?
Fucking
Here conditioners they call it in your car like, you know
Yeah, see doesn't even have litter boxes for all those cats in his place. He's I don't know how many cats he has and then
A few of them disappear because he lets them in and out and you know, they're out there and then I don't know what happened.
There's coyotes where he lives and he even said the coyotes got one of these cats.
And I've even told him keep them inside if you're going to keep them.
Make it like a little, you know, take them out, you know, if you want, but get a little
cataric thing outside so they're safe if you need to put them out for a little while.
Next time I'm doing an adult resort, man, fucking too many kids, screaming.
Ana pecanese, the four cats are rescues.
And then his carpet looked horrible. I mean, yeah, they everybody clipped it. It's nasty looking
I mean, it's really bad. And you know, he looks like a meth take and he's gonna be or bathing
And then I won't know I just never came across somebody like that
Why do I keep getting muted
Wow, this is beautiful
But yeah, before I get like two hours, that is probably cool.
There's Sarah Summer, she gets banned because she mentioned Tony.
You cannot mention, why don't you just block Tony's name, you coward?
Toxic at this point.
This is the neighborhood of Washington Heights.
Oh, I have a piece of the nice first step down.
Oh, I like it.
And he's got me.
And hacking me.
It's like, you know, maybe I'll go like build up my rumble.
Dave, can you sell the price?
Which I'll go.
to look at my other channels or even my TikTok where I get a lot of love instead of just like,
yeah, I just have to keep going but you know, I'm going to sit down and sit down right now but
still I don't have any regrets beating into it. I'm a fighter, I'll fight back against it. I do
want people to, even if it means like you know the end of my channels, I don't really need to let
people know what's going on. He got kicked from the sandals and he's still fast to join.
Um the vape or whatever hey, she said she smokes vape
So you said she was waiting to get a vape from her
She said hers is just she just ran out and she wanted to get a vape. So why she's like, oh, I'm disgusting
I said whatever. That's not a fucking criticism. I don't care when someone smokes
Yeah, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I just want to fit. Yeah, I mean, there's a little bit more. I'm sorry
Anyway, I'll tell the truth even if I have like 10 minutes streams. You don't know
I don't know if anything positive to say but anyway
I guess, uh, I guess no one wanted it. He also had this woman. Um, that he apparently
I can't do that here. I do that here. When I was on panel with some people might
Wanting to talk, you might get a bang me for my life. Yeah, and I was confused like who this area. Yeah
Yeah, the same backstage like I was saying earlier
And uh, I didn't want her so I didn't bother with that. I just told him I don't know who she is
She knows Brandon because he he tried to assault her or did assault her
And then she showed up the other yes thing
Isn't it well and he was saying Karen wanted to talk to you. No, I didn't
Assaulted her. This was all online. How can there be an assault?
with her and she's got to be lying because she was laughing because she said what he
did to you tell us what he did to you and then there was another lady that didn't know either
one of them in the background and saying that she didn't know that woman either because that woman
was trying to talk to her she said I don't even know you and so when he asked her about Brandon
she said yeah yeah he tried to show something to me
And then the girl said and then he said a sexual assault and that other girl said what a sexual assault and that goofy girl
Was smiling like it's funny. She's not in her head. Yes, and she said yes
Well, you set that up though, right?
Because that's your friend and I forget her Noel. You said her name's Noel and then she pops up sometimes
on your channel
Should I unscrew these bolts?
I'm not unscrewing these bolts.
He's getting a good kick.
16 minutes, 51 seconds, and literally other than trolls
that he blocked, the only person in chat was Brandon Q.
See, that's all he had in chat.
When was Kate's video?
How old is that?
Oh, he's live now.
Probably like a month ago.
I got your number.
OK.
Get a job.
I got it.
OK.
That's a W per se.
Nice job.
I was ordered for sure for harassment.
Oh, yeah.
Well.
They'll just see what you're doing.
Yep, I got it exactly.
So there you go.
That was confirmed.
You know, I was pretty much out all day, so I didn't join panels or anything.
I did post a community post that was it earlier in the day, but this man needs to shave and
bathe and clean himself up.
He looks horrible compared to what he looked like when he first came on.
I don't know.
They showed a picture of him before.
It's obvious he's doing meth.
And I will start giving away a letter at a time of your address.
Longer you can ask me.
Can you imagine what kind of losers those people are?
Oh, he's going at Alec.
You're the winner.
Congratulations.
Thank you so much.
And your Christmas tree, maybe.
Maybe I'm in an Easter egg. Who knows?
Yeah, such a victim perpetual victim. Yeah, right people that left or and he's victimizing people
But they can listen to like five seconds of a song, you know
I thought it was weird that he popped up out of nowhere on IG trying to add me
and I didn't even know him and I asked him how did you find my ID oh I found you
how because I have a completely different name on my IG and I don't add
people from YouTube on there so it's just weird you know he's a liar when we
talked me and Alex yesterday and we did talk twice
Um, she asked me, she said some, that she's not opening her chat sometimes, um, when she goes live, um, but, or panel, but she, and she said, maybe we should do a panel just me and you. And I said, well, I hope we don't talk about drama.
But I think it needs to be mentioned and what he's done. I mean, people have a lot of lives though.
And you don't even have any
Karen has a life no one believes that
Get a life and stop talking about Alex and going on about oh, she talks to my family this and that and then you're gonna play an old clip
She clearly has no life because she's contacting everybody and fucking stalking everyone so she has no life
Why is there a car boot?
iron
office tape holder
And the small garden on this room. It's a scavenger hunt
And that's a lot and I think she's framing
INX and me, and me and my dad as a suspect, and INX as the victim, and INX told the police
she would never do that.
I never told you any police.
And I said, well, it's weird, because you know what, INX isn't the one that took my
patio set.
No, I almost bought you one, and Gia said don't do it.
And she made a lot of that.
Yeah, I didn't know what to do with that.
But anyway, I'm defending you.
It was Verne that took her furniture,
and she cried about it for a couple of years.
And then she was over there talking to him again after that.
So, and I don't know what happened to Verne now,
but he was the one that did it.
And then he threatened to do it again later
when she pissed him off.
So I don't know.
She just, Crystal, you need to stop mentioning her names.
I asked you to stop, and you just don't.
So is um bar
Wait just a second until I finish this was with crystal. I mean just I I mean but I need to just like
This is old I think this is on IG I guess
with Bita. Bita told everyone to block me yesterday and then she has a nurse who asked me and INX and I said
Bita what is going on? I just woke up like I'm like half asleep like one eye open.
Bita doesn't care about things like that. You could be half gone on your pitch earning bathroom floor and she wouldn't care.
It's all about Bita, right?
She screamed at INX and INX and said,
I want nothing to do with you two loser bitches.
And you guys keep fucking talking about it, obviously.
Oh, just kidding.
Betah's ranting a lot of people, but then she blocked me.
But you know what, Betah?
Betah, you did say I'd never harass you.
I'm better.
Did you hear that, Betah?
And he's going to drag us back up again.
I guess it's no wonder that, uh, everybody on those, uh...
Sam, look at Wilbur, ready in the chest.
Damn, Wilbur, ready in the chest, too.
Can you off beta? It's kind of strange. Anyway, so I just want to kind of wrap all of this up. So
And saying I killed my grandma they did it in fact
I never said that you killed your grandmother
What I said, and I think that this is very important that you understand
Crystal do you want to go forward?
It's very important that you understand that I never said, Crystal, I need you to stop
interrupting me please or else we're going to be here all night and I can't stay here
all night.
Let me say something, Ropa, is a why I'm willing to stop about that, okay?
King, you're a POS who harassed my dad two days before my grandma died and that's what
started it.
Okay, so
Okay, so are you going to let me finish without interrupting me? Okay, so I never said that you
Killed your grandmother barb, right?
I think that it was a series of very unfortunate events where I mean you were like, you know performing and all of that
I was scared
Oh, I'm afraid that you were scared. I also believe you were worried, and I believe you're a danger on the road.
I was scared and worried, and I was worried.
What's not easy is that his tongue was in the bathroom.
I couldn't even breath.
What the fuck is happening?
The use about crystal is why you would think that anybody would tell you that I was a kid with you.
I am a kid with you.
That's what if I saw that you are that you that you were happy that I called out
Oh, what's up, brother?
Not much, man. How you doing?
I'm doing great, bro.
I know you heard me over there at Christine earlier.
I did. Yeah, I heard a bit of it.
So she gave me shit.
She was like, what the fuck?
Why are you joining Psyche's panel and not giving him shit?
Are you ready to hear that from her?
Or do you think it's only double standard?
I don't know.
So you already know.
She nags on me for this shit, too.
Yeah, people get harassed for coming to my show.
Do I harass anybody for going to her show or be the show?
No.
But they're harassing me, OK?
And they say I'm stalking them.
And they're, like, actively harassing me and slandering me.
OK.
For the record, Psyche, the thing that is,
and I don't agree with when you have Brandon Q around,
let that stand.
Is it bad for the show for, like, a bug?
I
said I know where I stand on these people's signals. I don't like either Brandon or Karen
But I guess we have to tell everybody that every stream
But even though we made that aware it's everyone every stream
Somehow they hear everything but that part because they don't care. They just want to like there's looking for a reason to hate me or
So might be for another reason or their jealous or something
I don't know they have all everything they're throwing everything at me
But the kitchen sink and even like there was a kitchen sink throw it at me, too. Thank you. I installed it
They'll hear everything except that part like right now. Let's say that was like maybe two minutes of us just talking right there
Yeah, and I'll do a 10 second clip of her voice right now. Yeah, what do you want like?
What do you want?
You see a fucking mess head. Well fuck you like I think I think what these people want the people that complain about it
Are that if we do come up we're supposed to be going at psych like the whole time
so until we get kicked off that's what we're supposed to be doing apparently I believe so I didn't know that's what they
Make me believe that's what they want. Yeah
but at the end of the day it's like
Psych's a grown man. Well, and it's ineffective too because psych's not gonna listen to that. He's just gonna kick his off
He's gonna say go away. Yeah, go away. Fuck you. Fuck you your brand. You don't have a wrench anymore. Fuck you
Right
So it doesn't work doesn't do anything
He could do whatever he wants, right? Yeah
Doesn't mean we agree with it. I'm right and I don't agree with some of the stuff that Sykes done. He knows
So it's like, oh, what are you?
What are you doing over there? I was like, don't tell me what the fuck I can and can do
Enough of that shit. I don't know these are
Online games to me. It's like I don't know
I, I call it the fake cry baby bullshit.
I wonder that fake rage, they fake rage.
Oh yeah, fake outrage.
Yeah, clutch my because she had good times on mind you, good
times put out a shitload of information on page out.
but oh, I wasn't aware of that. I didn't hear that I heard I heard
I don't know exactly what he put out, but I heard that he did yeah
Oh, he's a scumbag dude. He called me a psychopath when I tried to get on he calls everybody's something that he is
Yes, we saw a stocking charges on him, bro. The guys are weirdo. Yeah
I don't have any I've never done anything criminal like against the person like you know
It's all been like no victimless crime basically, you know, right?
Okay, what's with Christine's channel Christine 6666? I believe so, but I think she must have taken it down because somebody can't a good time said the n-word
Oh, did he yeah?
Well, let's see. Let's see what handed up crashing out. Oh, Jesus
Does a harry joined and he was like, what are you fucking doing? You're smoking you're drinking. What are you doing?
Life is up. It's still up
And he was like what the fuck is it to you you fucking and then boomie crush though
No, no, no, no we listened to it already. I haven't heard
Well, I heard it for you. It's okay. Don't worry
Yeah, I heard some of it that I went swimming
So, where are you the thing that is are you in Mexico? Yeah, I'm in Cancun. I'm about 80 kilometers from Cancun
But it's you know, I'm in the Maya Riviera. Oh
Look out of here
believe I was there maybe two years ago yeah yeah it's nice man it's a beautiful
resort it's five star resort I have on the premiere plan so I have all these
extras and it's fucking pretty wild man though you should definitely attend the
the evening the evening events
evening what the evening events they usually have yeah yeah yeah there's a
theater and all that shit yeah I'm gonna go check all the shit out
self-awareness playing a video but showing me
What the fuck is going on?
We're talking dude!
What the hell?
Do this shit when you're alone!
Oh man.
What the fuck is going on?
Do you have ADD, dude?
What was it, ADHD?
Yeah.
Psyche, what the fuck is going on, bro?
We literally just had your back and you're gonna fucking put music over a stalker.
Hello!
Please, thank you.
Because I feel blessed. I don't do a lot in my community.
There we go.
I don't stream.
I don't talk about it.
That's like a three-hour stream.
We're not watching the whole thing, are we?
Come on, Psyche, dude. Come on.
I don't need to.
Oh, my God.
Going after Amanda, calling her vet.
Psyche.
She needs a crane.
She's sick.
Oh, my God.
She's a cop caller.
What's she supposed to do to protect her 80-year-old dad?
Jesus Christ.
What do you want her to do?
So what are we doing here? Thank you. Anyways, yeah, I definitely suggest attending the events in the evening
Telling women they've had abortions because their dad dads have a pregnant. Yeah, I'm gonna check it out man for sure
It's disgusting
Wearing clothes that is very light because it could be hot in there dude. It could get but hey. Oh, yeah
I know it want to go low
Now get comfortable. No, no, no long pants. No long shirts, bro. It gets hot, you know
You're gonna enjoy
My phone take the take the videos
I'm enjoying it so far. I only arrived last night and I'm loving it already. It's only fully been your up a day
And leave me
My name out of your I can't wait. I can't I love going on vacation
If you want, I don't really need it, but at least it gave you the picture. You want to do the bed in that?
Sorry, let's move on
If I only arrived last night, so there's not really anything to be done. Maybe tomorrow tomorrow. Yeah easy did classy easy did
Yeah, that's fine. Two o'clock, whatever.
Number one's all the way. Don't worry about it.
Thank you. You can have them all. I don't need a win.
Good guy, the thing that is, guys.
Same thing's happening. Good guy, the thing that is.
You know, Jeannie, and I'm sorry.
I don't really know. What a nice guy.
Sticker chick, I've watched her a couple of times
when I've been being, you know, the Canadian person
and the person out in Cali.
Um, I've kind of been seeing what's going on
and I'm sorry for sticker chick that's happening to her.
Well, Doctor, are you still... Oh, my God.
We're talking. It's disgusting, too.
What the hell?
Summer can beat me up rogue. I don't care. Oh my god. Do you not understand that? Well, I'll just talk over this
Yeah, I'm part of the problem. Anyways
um
Now
You are over there for how long a week. Oh wait. Yeah. Nice. Yes. Nice, dude
Nice
Psych now. What's up with the whole neighbor that he got kicked out? Oh
Yeah, hello. Hello, I think he might have moved. I don't think I kicked out
You don't think you got kicked out?
Probably not.
But how, though? He broke a whole fucking window.
Well, it got the window got fixed, and he probably, maybe he had a bill.
I don't know how I'm gonna do it with the people that run it.
I'm just saying, I would have kicked his ass out of there. Fuck that.
You ain't fucking, you ain't staying here breaking windows? Get the fuck out of here.
I haven't seen him in a while. I haven't seen him. I moved, I'm not sure.
Were you friends with that person before that happened?
No, never.
never okay
Does that guy own a place or is he renting it?
No, renting.
He's renting, yeah.
Roy, Roy.
Damn, Psych.
Yeah.
But I mean, how are you doing mentally?
How are you?
Are you stable?
Are you okay?
I'm good.
I've been smoking this vape.
This vape is called a boost.
Is your life at danger?
My life at danger?
No, I don't feel like it's in danger.
Psych, that reminds me.
Don't you think you're overdoing it a bit with summer?
Well, yeah, but I got mad at her because she wouldn't let me talk or like, you know, express myself
And then like I was trying to like, you know pay five bucks
So I could have a minute to speak and they wouldn't even like can you see me when I was asking for that?
But then I got really mad and like, you know triggered and stuff
You know, I'd probably do an apology, but I went too far, but I never yelled.
I just looked stupid yelling and stuff, and I lost my cool.
And it's like just what they want.
You know, it's just like they want me to like fucking get mad and stuff.
So, I mean, I fell into the trap and I drank too much.
And I was like, you know, really super of trickery to that point.
Because I felt like I was just not being able to get my side of the story out or
others. I think this is a year for crashing out.
We're all crashing out this year.
Do you think you could offer her an apology right now?
Well, I'm sorry that I yelled and stuff, but, you know, I don't think that it's like, you know, sure
Well, once you say but, the whole apology just goes down the drain
I'm sorry that I yelled, I'm sorry that I yelled, and I'm sorry if I, like, got said anything like
I don't think I said anything too personally bad about her, but I was just mad, you know
Roy, Roy
Thank you for calling her a whore and stuff, man
Oh my god
Oh, no, I'm, I don't know. Maybe I said something like that. I'm sorry.
It was just, you know, she's called me FHG before.
We just like, we, we, we, we, we, we held each other.
We've always been a little bit kept up, but it's like, it's just weird.
Cause I was like, I just, I asked her for five minutes of her time.
I wanted to ask about her like doxy because she's been so seriously dox.
And I thought she might have some good information for me or to like, you know,
I can have five minutes. I understand she's very busy and stuff.
But she was like, oh, I don't want to get involved in the Alexandra.
So I'm like, I'm not trying to go involved.
And she's like, okay, but then she had no she didn't have five minutes and then she did have like five minutes
We're like, okay, you know get you over there and like be cock on up or whatever with the Alex and stuff in her chat
And so it's fine. I don't care who shat your head. It's like but it's like, you know
I thought we were friends and like she's a managing mod here
So I would like been to her backwards to make her happy and stuff
Well, if you were friends then you probably should have been a little more understanding that she didn't have the time at the moment, right?
It's time to sit in these chats with for anything else, you know, but it's like when I would show up. She would like just run away
I just like went into like in front of and say I wasn't even able to like get my point up
And I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Thank you the biggest scumbag on earth, right?
Now I'm just gonna say the worst, I'm gonna say the worst.
I'm no offense, but I find it hilarious when you're like, oh yeah, I'm just the biggest piece of
shit on the fucking earth. I'm worse than fucking Saddam Hussein. It's just, I'm horrible.
Wow.
It's all right. It's like it's all right. Yeah. Yeah, I mean it's like I mean it's like I've let people some people know me
But it's like even are you come over your company's call me scumbag and yeah, like, you know
Well, I say, oh, you know do this and this like why don't you do this and this and it's fine
I mean, it's like I like having your right view as friends and stuff right Roy
I do but I don't like when are you talking on my back or third and then you go over talk behind your back
What are you doing on other shows that you talk shit about?
When did I talk shit about you now?
Here we go.
Well.
Not since you got your mods, so just hang on.
Oh, okay. See, so we got to correct that when you used to talk behind my back.
Yeah, see, we all have to remember, things are in the past,
even what happened yesterday is in the past.
And I have a short-term memory.
So all these conflicts and stuff, I have no idea.
I'm just very confused.
I don't want to go down the ramp. Roy. Roy.
Just saying, I'm sorry if we all like to start over or whatever.
I don't know.
It's like, I'm like willing to forgive anybody, you know, anybody, but it's like, no one's
apologizing to me.
Everyone's asking me for apologies.
People are telling me to shove my apologies in my ass and go hug a cactus and all kinds
of horrible things, you know, and it's like, I'm just trying to like fucking like entertain
people and I have a fun show and like, you know, it's like Harvard ever turned on me
and they turned on me, doxing and fucking like, you know, harassing me and, you know, and
then it's like, no one really cares.
And like, then there's like a don't donate to me.
It's like, I mean, it's like, come on.
It's like, I make things just so, so hard and terrible for me.
Like, oh, especially when I leave, I mean, it's like,
really, it's like, you know, the more you complain about that,
the more you complain about Alexander using your parents' names and all that stuff,
the more she's going to do it because she knows it's getting to you.
No, it's not even it. It's like, you know, it's like everybody here
It's like it's like the like a lot of the chatter just trolled like a lot of like, you know, people
Yeah, yeah, the text messages you say, oh leave me to alone leave me to alone you and I GG er
You're yeah, yeah, that sucks. Dixie the hell and all kinds of horrible things. You think those are all Tony
Well, I don't know if they're all like a laughing.
I think it's been staged because it's like the heat.
They're just not staged.
He's he has a busy life.
He doesn't do that to the same picture.
Like that I get is a picture he's using of it.
It's like Ruby to his cousin or something.
That's like the same really ugly woman.
And it's like, that's his picture.
And it was like, I get those pictures.
I also get many V man since picture being
like shaving his vagina and stuff.
On the surface that sounds hot, but I know what mini Manson looks like. So
So it's not hot
No, it's not
So funny that he just said they show me a
Picture of mini Manson and him shaving his pussy. Yeah, that makes no sense
And you know about these they're transgender people, you know
They're women, they have vaginas.
He is shaving his pussy, that makes no fucking sense.
There's a big razor next to it, it's like horrifying.
Horrifying.
And then there's also a picture of it with a big bladder fetish.
He has his bladder completely extended.
What?
A bladder fetish?
Yeah, a mini man says a bladder fetish.
Oh my goodness.
I like him.
I hope he comes back to the show.
I mean, he's kind of mad because I hit,
I have my videos on private right now just for like, yeah.
What the hell?
Shout out to Aldo.
He said he wants to join your panel.
Pictures of Groovy Jimmy's like whole family
and stuff like that.
Oh, here's Rain.
Hey.
Hi, sweetheart.
Hey, Rain.
Good.
So yeah, these other two are haters.
I was telling them, hey, let's make him come here.
But no.
Wait, wait, what?
What I didn't hear you said out of my fucking face bitch. Whoa, what the hell?
She hates bold people. So I'm already in her bad books. Just right off the start. I'm in her bad books. So
I'm sorry
It's not your fault psyche is these other two weirdos shut up. Hey, what the fuck you shut the fuck up
Nobody even knows who you are, bitch
I was about to give you a compliment I actually like your voice, but fuck you bitch
Fuck you
Maggle
Shit, bitch rain rain. I'm in Mexico. Are you? Yes?
What do you want to see? I'm in Mexico. Well, I'm trees. I don't know if you're in California or Mexico. You could be lying
I'm in Mexico
What part?
Thank you. My area my area about 80 kilometers from Cancun idiots
you gotta speak Spanish when you're in Mexico
I gotta what? While I'm here?
You gotta speak Spanish when you're in Mexico
I'm a tourist man, tourists don't have to speak the language
Yeah you do
No, we're entitled, tourists are entitled
No, you're not entitled to shit
Yo, who is this bitch bro?
Rain it's awesome
She came in here way too red hot dude way too red hot. She usually does
You can't take the latina heat bitch. Yeah, shut the fuck up you fucking whore
How am I a boy? I have a boyfriend bitch, but you don't have a girlfriend much less a wife
I don't have a girlfriend. I have a whole wife stupid
That's not JTA. What's less a wife?
Idiot go fuck yourself
This bitch is Mexican disgusting nevermind
So what if I'm Mexican fucking hater?
be mad about it be mad about it disgusting you're disgusting whatever the
fuck you are this is what she does nah she came in wait yeah this is this is
this is how I make friends bitch this is how I make friends to you fucking bitch
yeah it's how I make friends Mexicans fucking suck
I'm not sure to tell everybody that here. That's what you think. I bet you a Mexican broke your heart, bitch
No, cuz I've never been with one. They're all disgusting
Idiot, so what are you white or something? I'm fucking Philippine. I got a little dick, bitch
Nice, you're you're Filipino. It'll know you're ill
No, you
The way you sign is so fucking disgusting. Oh
disgusting
sickening sickening. At least I speak Spanish. I'm like you fucking want to
be. I don't want to be Spanish. I don't need to speak it.
Bitch, I'm just doing it. Is that all you could say?
Why do you have a Puerto Rican accent? What's the
You're Puerto Rican, bitch.
No way, yo soy mexicano.
Ew.
I sounded pretty gay right there.
I work in Maya Riviera way.
Let me go clean the toilet thing it is.
Bitch, I live in Mexico.
Who the fuck are you?
Grossie or whatever.
Jocie, grossie, whatever the fuck you are.
Hey.
All right, you know what psych I'm out of here. I can't stand this. I'm out of here. No good leave bitch
You're fucking fake. Anyways, like he doesn't need big friends
We chased Arthur away Arturo good
Good
He's so fucking weak. Yeah
Arthur she got a W there. I'm sorry. Hi Chanel
Yeah, he could go cry about it. So what are you doing today rain? Is it a work day for you?
Okay, it's my day off actually. Okay. Enjoy it. Thank you. You're welcome. So what's up, Psyche? What are you doing?
Well, you know, I don't know like a new day a new new person mad at me
Like who who who do I got a beat up next? Well, I don't want you to beat up anybody because she's like, you know, I guess
well
Yeah, but she's mad at me. I don't know. I mean, it's I'm scared
I don't want you to get like some of these women are like are crazy the back here weapons
My carry weapons I
Don't know like knives and stuff like that. Oh my god, you forget. I'm an Aztec warrior. Like I'm not afraid of shit
Good
Like every about yeah, we're watching these stoner scribe and it's like pretty pretty good. Yeah, the stoner scribe videos
Yeah. You showed me. Yeah, I'm ready. Okay. Don't play one now. Actually, I'm going to drop anyways. I'm going to go swimming. Okay. Go swimming. Take pictures of your breathing suits. No. My private messages. No. Okay. Okay, rain. Nice seeing you again. Not really, but I'm just being friendly. Okay. All right. So I talked to you later. See you guys. Hi. I mean, bye. Okay.
Oh, I can't hear you now. So like you hang on. Let me come back. Okay. I'm back. Cool
So, yeah, those other two are haters. I mean you see how fast they drop like they can't take they can't take the heat
Yeah, yeah, they can't and then you say eggs they out of the kitchen, but let's see. Hold on
I'll find a funniest one. Let me see this has to be
You know these people though in these videos. No, oh
German ladies here. Hi German lady
I drew a man lady. Okay. Well, this is like something a bug. Let me see
This is a short one
Okay
Let's see it
What do you want big clips? Maybe I left it maybe I left it in the uber. I need you to call my phone dad
Why don't you just call them back? No, I don't know how to do that
Maybe I left my phone somewhere here call my phone dad
Almost twice your reign and I thought of that shit. You're telling me you can't figure out how to call them
All these smokes, just call the fucking phone, dad!
God damn it, all right.
I don't hear anything.
Because the phone's not there.
Fuck, I'm about to left it in the Uber!
Why the hell do you care, sir?
God damn much.
You got three of those phones, don't you?
You can buy another phone with those ski angels
you're always bragging about.
Dad, I live streamed literally yesterday
and I was there for several fucking hours
and do you know how many cash apps I received?
One, one, uno.
yo tengo uno dinero uno peso one there's a McDonald's down the road that's
hiring I can't fucking work that job dad I suck don't ever take me I just gotta
get I just gotta get Julio to stop taking my money do you have
Emilio aka little shit aka Julio that was a little nickname that I made up for
Well, I think so. He's definitely such dick, and he takes some steals all my money, so he's probably a Jew.
Boy, what the fuck is wrong with you?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
All I need to do is do a little bit of leprechaun hunting.
Gotta take his little pot of gold before he uses it into some kind of gay sex ritual, involving his anus.
I think I know a pretty good leprechaun hunter too.
All that fits in about the other phone, and you had another fucking one the whole time.
Shut the fuck up already, dad!
All right, everyone. Good morning, good afternoon, or good evening, whatever time it is,
wherever in the world it is that you are. Welcome once more to another live stream of
I am your hostess, Alexander Mayers.
It seems there is a group of people
that has helped bent on telling me exactly...
What the actor known as David D'Cou who plays the character of Schemast Gandy
I said about me as of late. So this is your chance. I am giving you one hour
You have one hour to get whatever's on your chest off your chest
I would appreciate it if you gave me a time frame a time frame
Maybe a time stamp of the things he said the same kind of evidence that I tell people that I have you have one hour to tell me
What he said
Grappler Six claims that he was called the N-word several times and then blocked.
Grappler Six, are you African-American?
Yes or no. It's a simple question.
Isn't it one time too much for a white guy to use the N-word in 2023? Wow.
Well, I'll tell you, if I could jail every single white person that has ever used the
n-word even once, I don't think we would have very many white people in America.
Should every black person be jailed who calls a white person a cracker?
What about every black person that has called a Latino a spick?
Sometimes people say things that they let her regret and don't mean.
Somebody called me that recently.
Well, excuse me for having white friends.
Excuse me for not thinking that all white people are evil.
This is the phone of Alexander Melody Mayers.
Yo, Alex, it's your boy, Ski.
Mr. David Taku, I was about to call you.
I needed to do my news segments very soon,
and I was going to consult you.
What's up?
Oh, I'm just letting the peasants
that hate you try to express themselves.
I'm going to let them try to persuade me to the narrative that you're a terrible person.
Oh, before I started live streaming, I was just finishing up a book that I was reading while
I was taking a break from the book of Leviticus. It's called, uh, Mein Kampf?
Mein Kampf, I think that's what it's called. I don't know how to pronounce it exactly. I believe
I've been reading an English translation of it, however, and I have to say there are
a lot of things in that book that resonate personally with me.
Oh, well, uh, I don't know if you can give me a hand with Emilio again.
What is he doing now?
He's taking all of my fucking money, Alex!
I can't even make a dime off of any of the live streams that I make.
Fucking reaches of sifting off me.
David, there's something you must understand.
Obstacles do not exist to be surrendered to, but only to be broken.
And Emilio Bellani is just one of those obstacles that the Lord sends your way to test your character.
Just as Jesus walked through the desert and was tempted by the devil,
so too do you, Mr. David D'Cou, devout Christian, have to bear demons in the flesh.
Can I get your help?
Mr. David D'Cou, I am your friend.
Everything I do in supporting you, I do because I believe today.
My conduct is in accordance with the will of the Almighty.
the Lord Jesus Christ.
I will give you all the support of this channel
to back up your own.
Thank you so much, Alex.
You see all the support that I get
doing what I do on the internet.
Hey, what are you talking about?
Hey, I was talking to Alexander Mayers.
And she's making me, and then we're making sure
that everybody on the street, so that he's a good guy.
And that Emilio is a little shit, dick-sucking bitch,
and he just wants to ride on my dick.
Is it straight? Is he a prostitute?
No, not really. Not full time anyways.
Does she not like James neither?
No, not really.
My son is just talking to more and more trash. It breaks my heart.
I guess that's better than you breaking my arm though.
Okay David, let's review everything that I will be putting on the channel over the next few days.
Yeah, did you tell everybody about horse face fucking dogs?
I've already made an extensive segment on it already.
with your testimony as evidence?
You think people are going to think that's proof?
Proof?
We tell them that we have proof and that's proof enough.
It is very good fortune that for us two people that are in the upper echelon of celebrity
and fame, it is very fortunate that people do not think they don't need proof.
Jennifer Katz, she is having sex with animals.
Yeah.
Stone or scribe threaten me. Do I have the proof? Of course I have the proof, extensive evidence and proof.
But I'm not going to show it to anyone. Why would I? Because I told you that I haven't. I follow.
And when it comes to Miss Jennifer Katz, there are simply so many different things that are very natural to people of the Jewish faith.
that seem horrifying to normal people like us.
But it seems now that it is this group of people
that are coming now to victimize us.
We, the followers of Jesus Christ.
So you got horse face covered?
Covered.
What about Julio?
Let me tell you what I think needs to happen
with Amelia Vellani.
My feeling as a Christian points me to my Lord and savior
as being a fighter.
It points me to a man who, once in loneliness, surrounded only by a few followers,
recognized these people for what they are and summoned them to fight against them.
I am a nonviolent, peaceful person at my core.
However, I am a woman, and clearly my opinion is different because of that.
When it comes to men, if there's one thing I know, it's that sometimes disputes need to be solved physically.
Do you hear me? Oh, hang on. I can't hear you again. Shit
Handsome oh, thank you so much. This is so ugly. Miles sad. Oh
It's a lot. I'm a little stoned
Ray makes me happy. So yeah, like who was that guy anyways?
That is Stoner's scribe who just does like little skits and stuff, but like like
Stoner's scribe? Yeah. Oh
Never heard of this person. No, I don't know. He's just tagging us and videos and stuff
But he's pretty funny, but yeah other people I know so it's kind of funny, but yeah, maybe you didn't
like he went on that so
Anyway, you said it was gonna be short. That was like 30 minutes. I'm so sorry. It was actually 10 minutes
Well, you know like in chat time, it's like
a minute equals to like, you know, an eternity.
Yeah, I'm sorry, well, what do you want to talk about?
So congratulations to Spain for winning the World Cup.
Oh, is that why everyone is yelling outside?
Yep, they beat Argentina.
That's pretty cool.
Well, congratulations, congratulations.
Yeah.
And what else?
Who is Bakelips?
Bakelips?
Have you ever met Bakelips?
Bakelips is like some, it's I think somebody that like,
you know, it likes me.
He's saying that you remind him of Legally Blonde
when she's in bed and throws chocolates at the TV.
Is that true?
Yeah, Argentina cheated, but they still lost.
So, they tried.
Yeah.
So what else is going on?
That's like Legally Blonde.
He's a brunette.
Well they tried. They were trying to cheap their way to a win, but they couldn't.
Well, that's so sad. I found this video, it says ban cartoons. Do you want to watch some of this?
It's been banned after one episode. I want to see if you remember any of these cartoons.
I think they might be making these up.
I don't believe these cartoons actually exist.
I think these are recent creations that they're saying.
If you want to kick me off the panel,
you have to pay $500 just like you, just cash out.
Exactly, here we go.
So let's see if this is any good.
Have you seen these?
Let's see if you remember any of these cartoons.
And we'll like pause through here.
Here we go.
This one.
What do you want me to do?
Lift up the island so you can sweep under it?
It wouldn't hurt to lock in on it. Check it out, just in case.
The 1970s were supposed to be innocent.
A time when kids poured cereal, turned on the TV,
and escaped into Saturday morning cartoons.
But behind those flashing colors and laugh tracks,
something strange was happening.
This was the decade when animation got weird.
Studios were experimenting with psychedelic art,
political satire, and counterculture themes,
sometimes by accident.
sometimes on purpose.
Animators fresh out of the 60s hippie movement brought surrealism,
dark humor, and even adult undertones into children's television.
And what came out of it was a collection of shows
so bizarre, so completely out of step with the times,
that networks didn't know whether to laugh or cancel them.
Others mixed rock music with time travel, or monsters forming pop bands in haunted mansions.
A few shows even blurred the line between morality and madness,
airing for a single season before quietly disappearing into television oblivion.
These weren't your typical Saturday morning cartoons.
They were fever dreams that accidentally aired for kids.
So today,
We're diving into the 15 strangest, most unbelievable cartoons of the 1970s.
Shows so odd, you'll wonder how they ever made it to broadcast.
Before we start, make sure you subscribe to Vintiverse.
Hit like and tell us in the comments which weird retro cartoon from your childhood still haunts your memory.
Number 15, Wheelie and the Chopper Bunch, 1974.
Imagine a world where cars talk, fight, and fall in love, and not a human in sight.
That was Wheelie and the Chopper Bunch.
A short-lived Hanna-Barbera experiment that looked like a cute kid's show but played
out like a fever dream on wheels.
The star, Wheelie, was a red Volkswagen Beetle who spoke entirely in honks and beeps, yet
somehow had a full romantic relationship with another car named Rotary.
Together, they constantly battled a gang of motorcycle bullies called the Chopper Bunch,
led by a sneering biker named Chopper.
Motorcycles mocked the cars, wheelie outsmarted them using cartoon physics, and everyone laughed in a world that made no sense.
There were no humans, no logic. Just cars living out a parody of human society, complete with love triangles, races, and revenge plots.
Executives thought it would be the next speed buggy.
But instead, it confused children and terrified parents.
The sound design was bizarre, the humor oddly aggressive, and the idea of a sentient car
world before cars was too uncanny for audiences.
Um, yeah, I don't remember any of these cartoons.
I'm Gen Z, I'm sorry.
Yep.
Well, but you haven't saw Wheelie in the Chopper gang.
No.
You don't remember the motorcycles?
I've never seen these.
Like I said, I'm Jim Z.
Oh, have you ever heard of this comedian called Roy Jay?
No.
Who's that?
Oh, he was a famous comedian in the 70s,
but no one remembers him.
And it's like, I think he would have been remembered,
but he's apparently a real clips of him on shows.
He was also in a commercial too,
but I wanted to see if someone was calling me.
That's like a fuse.
I feel like that's for boomers, I don't know.
Yeah, you're gonna like, you're gonna love it.
You're gonna love it.
It might be, no, it's not for boomers
because this is in the 80s, he was a comic.
And you have to tell me if you remember this guy.
Okay.
Tell me if you remember him. His name is Roy J. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Yeah, he was known to wear pajamas on stage and like
Sound like Robin. He's supposed to be British. We sound like Robin Williams
I've got to talk to someone about this chick that I love.
For giving her to me, I thank my lucky stars above.
She's everything I want, my true sweet heart, my turtle dove.
But she's weird and fat and ugly, but the only one I love.
Yes, it's love.
Love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love.
Spooky love.
I gaze into her face and it's then I realize I've seen potatoes on my plate with better looking eyes
Looking skywards, Concord knows he's only half the size of the conca darning her face between those two mince pies
But it's love!
If she ended Mr. Universe, she'd certainly win my vote
women her size on born they're long just like a boat with leg makes round the
wrinkles she still rise up and float so to protect the easily frightened she always wears a coat
but it's all right so she wanted to be placed front and center on the stream
and then that's all she provided that's all she could do she said she was gen z more like gen
Wow, how'd you find her rain? Yeah
Is their name rain because you know when it rains I should be putting you to sleep
Wow, what a boring individual
Wow, I'm sorry say that you had a big put up with that
She's fucking sucks dude. She didn't provide anything
She was fucking boring. She was bitchin about put me up on panel right now. I was behind
So but anyways, like I mean, let's get back to the Christine situation
Okay, she she says that I'm supposed to shit on you every time, right
That shit's just not gonna happen cuz it's it's redundant
You get me? Can you right now say this out of your mouth, say, Steve does not agree with
most things I have done. And he has been vocal about it.
I've let you say everything you want to say.
Can you say that?
I love you, Arthur.
What the?
I love you so much.
So you can't be saying that and then petting your pussy chill
Chill chill chill chill chill we're not doing that
Anyways, how's it going there brother?
Now for the record I called you brother cuz they called I call everyone brother now people gonna be like, oh, you know, he's a
He's supporting everything Sike has done. I'm a synthesizer
sympathizer
Everything and anything, you know, just because I called you brother. No
He is a weird motherfucker. He had done weird shit. He knows it. I know it. We all know it
Okay
Shit, but anyways, Sike
Now I've noticed that sometimes Sam and joins panel here and yeah
He acts like he doesn't want to be here, right? You're like, I'm just sitting on him. I just shouldn't know him
He likes to come and show me. Yeah, bullshit. He has a he's a people matter fetish
And then I mean, let's be honest. You were saying to the day I'm blended police station. You never went, right?
The police came here
Yeah, like I said, you didn't go.
Um, everybody says, I'm going to the police right now.
And then I asked them to frisk me,
and they're like, no, you're not,
but you have to be under arrest first.
Frisk you?
Yeah.
You know what people are doing nowadays?
It was really cute, Kyle. Yeah.
What? You know what they've been doing nowadays?
What?
They go to the clubs,
and you know when the security has to frisk you,
they have to check you.
They just do that and then they walk away. They're like, all right, I just want it to be touched. Yeah, that's what I do
I I do that when I see like a hot like bouncer
It's like I'm gonna go in the club and then he like touches my butt and like my crops and then I
Say, oh, I was just saying hi
Jesus, that's an appropriate
We've been to Colt Codex recently, you should look at Colt Codex, see what's up there.
Alright, well I will be taking over the panel right now.
Ladies and gentlemen, Christine had a stream earlier today.
She was going bananas on people.
She really didn't give out many names.
to what people did.
All she did was tiptoe with the he, she,
they know who they are.
She knows who she is, he knows who he is.
And it's like, who are you talking about, lady?
And then she gets mad if you start assuming
who you think she's talking about.
You're the bad one for assuming who she thinks,
Throwing out assumptions because you're not giving me name
So from what I understood, I guess summer was calling her husband a PDF
That shit is crazy, dude
All because I guess they got together when she was 18, you know, and then she was saying how summer I
Guess she'd given money to summer and then she stabbed her in the back
You know again, this is what I'm going for from since no names are provided
while
The statements were being said
She said names later
But she didn't say what they're attached or who they're attached with
so
That's her fault
For not saying the names with what they did. But yeah, I feel bad for Christine
Whoever said malicious shit like that to her
And then I think she said that people were making fun of her health that's that's about that's bottom of the barrel shit
You know, I would never make fun of
Anybody self like that. Nope. Nope. Nope much. I don't get along with Christine or we go at it
I can assure you this Christine. I would never make fun of your health
Never. I ain't I ain't about that. I don't do that
You know
Bust your balls with the little, you know, your age sometimes, but remember your health. That's that's not me
That's not funny, right?
But anyways, what's going on chat today is a
Monday, I'm still a little hurt. We didn't win yesterday. I actually don't want to talk about it. So
Lo lamento boludo me duela me duela me duela a un boludo
It still hurts. It still hurts. Shout out to my fellow Argentines out there. Shout out to Calle Vosso. Shout out.
Anyways, what is going on? How's it going, reality? Nancy in the chat. We got midnight in the chat. What's going on? Midnight.
We got Tracy in the chat. What's up, Trace? Oh
You know, how's it going beats?
Who else is in the chat?
That's big Bethany. That's not Peter. It's big Bethany. We got a lady back three. Nice
time
She's in here. We got
We got clumsy in the chat shadow. It's a clumsy though. Are these people all blocked or something? I don't understand
Who else to be a Ron? Oh shit puppets
Fucking puppets dude. Shout out to Ron. He does make a lot of money
I hope you could donate a dollar or two to psych it would go a long way and I would assume that psych would use the money for
good things
For his cats bitch. Why are you in here talking all that fucking bullshit when I leave? I told psyche I'd be back
Here we go. Yeah, I told psyche. I would be right back. You're a dumb bitch. Dude, you are boring as shit
I don't do a fuck what you think. I'm not here for your fucking validation. I'd rather watch fucking paint dry on the fuck
I'm not here for your fucking validation. You bald ass bitch
Really? I'm bald now bitch. Really?
You've been bald. You've been bald.
Brick
Idiot. Fuck you
Fucking bald long-nosed bitch, really really motherfucker you came up and I want to see what you look like
For you fucking creepy weirdo
You've got mad shit to say about me
You got mad shit about me bitch
Stay mad about it. Stay mad about it. You wish you had a man like me. You wish
Fuck can't hear this bitch now. Yeah, that's what I thought you wish you had a man like me you heard
Fucking Walmart headphones is what I thought making fun of my nose making fun of my no hair
Idiot. Oh, she's the biggest piece of shit on earth. Oh, she's the biggest piece of shit
Wow, what piece of shit you are you got mad shit to say you never even came up. Where the hell did psyche go?
How about you leave? I don't want to take over all the weirdo then leave
You wish you had a man like me you wish
Hell no, I got this man. I got the best man JT. I don't need you. I don't want you
Nobody does you wish you wish
Yeah, JT
Does he join panels too?
Not anymore. He's bored with it all
Yeah, just like you you guys are both boring
Makes sense. I think you're the boring one really
You're the one getting mad at everything I say. You're you came in red hot. Did you not come in red hot?
You call that red hot?
You called me a weirdo. You know what a weirdo is in New York. Are you aware of that?
Yeah, you're creepy. Oh
See, you know exactly what that means and you you want to throw out a jacket like that. I'm not from New York, bitch
Fuck you. You wish you were from New York
Yeah, no, I've been there. It sucks
Fuck you pig pig Phil's in there
You wish you wish that's why you fucking jump over the border every time in New York is fucking squalor and nobody wants to be there.
You're a fucking squalor squalor.
You don't even know what that means.
Spell it, bitch.
Educated you are.
Spell it.
I don't got to spell shit for you.
Exactly.
Idiots.
You're just mad because I'm like I made you look like a total clown to everybody
Also, how so when light in me? How so I bet you you're like five four or something
five five
You're fucking balls
So I think that's funny
You're fucking in so get the fuck away. So for the record I choose to be bald
Right. Right. Right.
Just like thing that is right. Right.
Right. Right.
Idiots, you guys choose to be bald. Right. Right.
Yeah. Yeah.
Just like you choose to fucking smell like jalapenos every fucking time.
You're looking weird, dude.
Like you guys are like over here trying to talk to a 26 year old.
I'm 26.
OK. And you're fucking old and.
Creepy the fuck is wrong now you're throwing out a jacket. What are you trying to say that is wrong with you?
What am I? What am I then?
Where what are you trying to assume?
You are old and creepy and bald
Throwing out jackets. I dare you to throw out a jacket. I don't want myself bitch
What are you talking about a jacket? Yeah, that's what I thought
idiot
Are you homeless you need a jacket
Yo, I know. I don't know what you mean, so you please come back to it. I can't stand this twat. I can't
This broad fucking sucks, dude
Doesn't lag. That's what you are
Does she have like musically or something or a tick tock to fucking dance to her some shit?
Somebody call ice on this bitch
Yeah, yeah, call ice when I'm already in Mexico. You don't fuck
They did their job nice
No, I went back voluntarily
You should be glad.
I am glad it's less fucking jumping beans over here.
Good. Good.
Idiots.
Idiota.
Oh, really?
Can somebody join the panel with me?
I can't. I can't with this one here.
I can't with this one chat.
Oh, la verga.
This is a no sablo.
Right here on the panel, ladies and gentlemen.
Here's the shit if you're a no sablo.
You're the no-subble.
Shut your bitch up.
Yo, chat.
I think Spanish fluently, unlike you.
Chat, chat.
Please, someone accompany me here at this moment.
I request somebody please, please.
You can call him Bob, but calling him all too far.
Ah?
Like, man, it's staying wherever you are, Rain.
I can't stand. Is that your indigenous indigenous name?
Rain. You've got Colombia, bitch.
Give a fuck about Colombia. Give a fuck.
They don't give a fuck about you.
Why you bring it up then?
Idiot, because Loki just said that his husband is from Colombia.
You dumb bitch.
Idiot. Idiota.
Are you a Chad, please?
We use joint panel. Hey Vader. Hey psyche. Can you drop the link for Vader? He wants to come up
Vader
Yeah, Vader
Darth Vader
That's my dog's name. How'd you know?
Vader's your friend too?
That's my dog's name idiot
Vader come up here
show
Look how mad I made this ball the weirdo
Mad by the way
mad
I fucking scouted him, Vader.
Really?
Wow, you...
You know, ever since you joined panel, you dropped the viewership here.
Way to go.
I don't give a fuck.
You know who you remind me of? You know, Bita?
No, I don't. I don't know that person.
I think you'd get along with her.
She likes to throw jackets out on people, too.
I don't know who the fuck you're talking about. I'm reading the chat.
Reading by the way, she's fucking you and being chat GBT to fucking translate what you guys are saying in the chat
Reading by the way
Reading by the way the old comments are hurting him exactly
Reading by the way idiot, but you're not make me crush up. You're about to make you crush
You're a crushed up. Look at you. You're fucking stimming
chat
You're stimming she doesn't want me to crash though. Okay, right? I'm on chat
Okay, it goes to point. Oh
Well, you know that weirdo too
Yeah, he was over there trying to be weird with me too fucking bald bitch
Fuck you. I was coming ghost the bald bitch, but the fact that you took offense to that
Stupid bitch you said to you know what two means?
No, thank you laugh it up brick
You can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't
Yeah, yeah, I mean, yeah, so yeah, Arthur's I mean, you have a good talk with them
Yeah, I actually have talked to Karen and we've reconciled and so it was just misunderstanding
So why are you friends with so many emotionally unstable people psyche? Well, I'm like maybe I'm a motionist too
Maybe maybe we can help each other. No, like I've seen you handle like people better way better
No, she's a good person and it's like, you know, she, I mean, she, we all say these
regrets and so I apologize if I said anything.
I mean, like when, when Shannon was coming after you, you handled that like a pro.
Well, yeah, but, but I just handled her like she handled me because she came at me very
aggressive, like a bull.
Yeah, I did.
Yeah, she was the aggressive one and you were just, you know, like trying to be friendly.
Like you were the bigger person.
Yeah, I mean, I try sometimes and it's like, you know, and it's like, but now it's like, I'm so attacked, like sometimes it's like, you know, really sensitive and like, you know, extra like, you know, I think someone was trying to give me a compliment today and I was like, you know, I just like skim their comment and I get all mad at them and I say about it again, it was actually supportive of me and I'm like, probably scary people away just by like.
Being poisonous and I apologize if I like, you know, go too far and get upset and stuff then
I'm not perfect either, you know
But yeah, you see the way he was talking shit as soon as he as soon as I drop off the panel like fucking
Trying to be all sneaky and shit fucking weasel
He's using it. He's using a different device
And he says he can't come at the moment. Okay. Oh, well Peter can't come up
What's not a different device?
You can't come up at the moment
Whatever that means. Yeah, come on Vader. Get your shit together
We're so lucky
At least Vader stopped by your stream psyche. Yeah, these were something by I
Mean he likes you when I remember when I dance for having my speedo and he like loved
Remember really like turn around
He likes my booty
You made you the star of the show. I loved it. I had a great time. It's so cute
Which I'm interested of virtual
Oh, I didn't like you like cubing guys
I I like it
Yeah
I'm sorry
Is he like Darth Vader, does he have like a Darth Vader outfit and then he oh yeah
Yeah, he has the helmet and everything but he looks like when he takes it off though
I mean just another Mexican guy really cute
No, he's Cuban. He has you know the curly hair going on
Oh like Sam it
No, no like Sam and Sam and he looks I don't know he looks like a rat
Yeah
Yeah, I have his real picture
He looks like a plumped out like a plumped up rat
Yeah, exactly
Like I have his picture right here
This has a little bit of a I on it, but this is as real as it gets
Nobody wants to see this
Just scared
Later
Who's that lady next to him? Oh, that's so that's just alone
Why does it look like me Manson without the makeup? Yeah, that's me Manson. Oh
Well, I didn't know he was like that
Sam and I
recognize that man. I
Didn't know he was into dudes with vaginas
He imagined what the armpits smell like
Nobody wants to imagine that
Yeah, Sylvester, I'm sorry. Oh, Nancy is Sylvester Stallone's friend.
I'm sorry. That's not the real Sylvester Stallone. That was Bita.
Why do you sound so down, Psyche?
I'm kind of down. Why are you sad?
I'm sad, but it's like, I don't know. I'm just kind of like laying down.
I've been, you know, I've been smoking a vape and like, you know.
Oh, you're just really high.
I'm a little bit high, yeah.
See me see me to sleep with some Mexican songs
In like who caracha
My best I don't really sing though, but I tried my best
Besame, besame mucho, como te amas tu especie de molati.
Wow, that's really good. Where'd you learn that?
Um, I've heard that movie. It means kiss me, kiss me a lot.
You heard this funny?
Yo quiero tapo beel.
No.
Oh, that's what we're American.
You're gonna talk about, I'm kind of craving that.
What's your favorite thing, a seven layer burrito?
Well, I normally get the beef cheese, beef cheesy burrito from there.
That sounds so good.
It is really good.
The beef and cheese coming together in your mouth.
Beef and cheese and rice.
Oh my God.
Sour cream?
Sour cream.
Yes
South Park where they're watching like the food network and it's all like it's like porn to them. Oh fuck. Yeah, make that creme fresh
Oh, yeah
And they're like, oh god, it's like, it's like, it's like porn to them because it's like the food network and it's like talk so sexual about the food.
Oh, get this in your fucking mind.
And the kids are like, they can't watch this food network anymore.
I forgot.
Or like that.
And then they started watching the true crime shows.
And like, you know, and then everyone's afraid.
Everyone's like, I don't know.
It's a great show.
Yeah, when was the last time you got Taco Bell?
Taco Bell, hmm, it's been quite a while.
Yeah, maybe a couple months ago.
Got a little coffee today.
Hey, hey, hey guys, hey guys.
I have coffee too, but now I'm hungry.
I got a free coffee today and I didn't steal it.
No, it was like free in the app.
Like it took 50 points.
Oh, what app, McDonald's?
I don't know, on the app, it was a big place I go to.
And McDonald's, I can get it for a dollar a cup
and then I can get everything.
Yeah, I love getting their coffee, it's one dollar.
They act like I like, I'm like robbing McDonald's
or something like that.
Like if it's some huge billion dollar corporation
and it's like, I'm like, you know,
Coffee from the machine where like, you know, they do free refills
They get to ask the person they have to like look at the cup it to go
Refill it and like that to say yes
I mean, it's like not like I'm like stealing the coffee and I didn't steal that spuckin cigar from that store like
Dealing if you have rewards
Yeah, I know I mean it's so crazy and it's like it's like, you know, so they allow me to refill it and stuff, so
free refills is like, yeah, like
It's still a thing, so why not so use it?
I don't know.
They don't want me to be just paying out my ass for everything while not donating anything
to me.
So it was like, what?
It's like, we're not donating anymore.
They're talking about money and stuff, I don't understand.
Vader's having a hard time getting up here. I don't know if he's banned from Stringard. Are you banned Vader?
No, because I haven't banned anybody on this one. I can't invite you. I can like turn off the
Add this thing where it's like, you know, I guess have to authenticate. I can turn that off and like maybe so we didn't have to authenticate
Let me see how I can do it. It says yes, and it says
Let me see
Yes, and it says
Okay, so I'll turn off the authentication
And then, guess, Steve, you were coming, guess, Mace.
Okay, so it's fine.
So it shouldn't work now, and no one's been banned.
Okay, so.
Try it again, Vader.
Yeah, I'm finished.
You don't have to authenticate.
Maybe that's what it is.
Because he was talking about.
He just said, I get banned for being too sexy.
Yeah, I wanna see him.
I wanna see him.
Fucking Vader.
Vader, I'm wearing my speedo.
You are just for you
Mm-hmm. Well, I've been wearing it since yesterday
He's not banned. I don't ban the sexy. I give them another chance
I didn't give say I think of the other people like saying another chance. Oh now it doesn't work again. Well, oh my god
He said he's using a different device. So he needs to create a new account. Well, I'll just do that. It's free
I don't have to show you this though. I'm gonna show you one more thing
So do you like that comedy?
What comedy that guy a bit of comedy
Like in general you think was funny. What do you think?
What comedy wait? I'm confused the guy that was like going spooky spooky love and you see him as girlfriend
I've never seen that. I was playing you missed it here. Well, look at this. There's a good
Tell me if this is a real commercial
Okay
Bater's being such a cock piece
He's being a what a cock piece. Yeah
No, he's just making a new account he's in this commercial. Oh, he's making a new account. He's in this commercial. I don't hear it
You hear anything? I don't hear it
Hey weird
They don't know the secret. I tell them, but they're weird. I'll tell you instead the secret is
Sparkling drinks from you know who
You look like a real commercial to me. Did you remember that person? No
Roy J. He was like a comedian in the 80s
They just I was born in the 2000s. Oh my god. Are you able to be on the show?
Yes, I'm 26. Okay. Oh my god. Well, they because then people will say, oh, I'm talking people 20 years younger than me
I'm such a pervert
No, because I'm taking and you're gay. So how does that work? I don't know if that's them
Um, but they said Joker was like a child and stuff like that was Joker's 26
How is that a child? I don't know. He has a full mustache and everything a child is under 18
Dumdums, I know is it ridiculous? They want to discriminate just because we're younger. I know and they're old
Yeah, did you like that comedy? I have more yeah, I'll say something on lawyer mind, okay?
Okay
Because this is what's really going on. It's when I first was introduced to him
Okay, here it comes
Okay, ready? You're reminded that we've blown hold on to your socks
Okay
Are you holding on to your socks?
I'm not wearing socks, but I'll wear socks right now. Okay, put some on
Hold on to them. You're in for a surprise
Let's see it. Okay
What if your entire legacy was tied to a 4chan post?
It's April 4th, 2025, an anonymous user on 4chan's paranormal exports drops a single
image of a guy in striped pajamas with, Discaption.
This is a demon writing itself retroactively into pop culture history.
You'll think this is a crap post, but you'll remember him from your childhood soon enough.
Reverse image searching the file name Royjpjs.jpeg into a search engine yielded no results.
Then suddenly he's everywhere.
The entirety of 4chan is sent spiraling.
People are claiming they've always remembered him.
Others say every video, every article, and every Wikipedia page is being generated in
real time.
This fucking Mexican fucking sucks.
Nobody gives a fuck.
Nobody gives a fucking tequila so she can fucking wake up.
You're crying about it, bitch.
No, I'm not gonna cry. I'm not crying about it.
You're already crying.
How so? Where are the tears?
Do you know what crying means?
You're fucking crashing out for no reason.
Crashing out, by the way.
Frashing out, by the way.
No reason. No reason to be so emotional.
No, I'm not emotional at all.
Just, uh, I'm just saying you're boring.
Well, nobody gives a fuck what you think psyche. Um, can you please enlighten the chat? Who is boring? Can you put that as a poll?
Who is more boring not doing whatever you want him to do bitch?
I've known him way longer than you. He knows that I'm suggesting. I don't give a fuck if you've known him longer
I know him better
Anyways, it's like it's like brother
psyche
You don't know about you
Saiki Papa, Papo, Saiki, Saikos, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki, Saiki
You're over here whistling at him and shit like he's a dog. What's the fuck respect?
Apparently whistling is that a
respect him bitch
Psychi, can you enlighten this oh how I've had your back numerous times in the past year or so?
No, cuz where have you been at when psyche was down all these times?
No, as he used to block me and he realized I had his back back then
Right. Right.
It's like he knows how fake you are.
That's who's like.
He's not talking to you.
He doesn't want to talk to you.
He's talking to you, bitch.
He was talking to me until your bald ass came up here.
Bald, by the way. How do you know I'm bald?
Somebody doxed you.
I don't know. Oh, wow.
So now this lady's doxing people now, psych.
I didn't do it.
Wow. We all did it.
Wow, dude.
Are we really gonna allow her to be around like this? She's fucking malicious. What are we doing?
How am I malicious? I just said somebody else did it. I didn't do it
Psych get her up and out of here. Get her up and out of here, dude
He's not doing what you're telling him to do
You don't control him anymore bitch. You don't control him. I don't you're right
Said can we put a little poll up up in the chat? He's gonna do what he's gonna do leave him alone bitch
So you know how much it would fucking hurt her feelings to know that nobody wants her in the panel
Right try to hurt my feelings, bitch. You can you know how much you would cry? I know how Mexicans love to cry
That's why they got that song
Sounds like you're going crying by the way psych yo come on brother where you at dog right here can we put up a pole?
No, no
You pay me I'll put up a poll seven some five dollars like you and I are interconnected like that bitch
Just uh, just a poll saying who is boring
We finish each other's sentences, we finish each other's sentences, that's how spiritually connected we are.
I did a poll on my own wall and it said, do I deserve to live?
And it was like 52% yes, 48% no.
I clicked yes.
Oh my god.
You know, and so I don't really like the polls anymore.
I mean, at one point it was like, 52%, you know, I don't deserve to live, 52%, it was like...
Well, psyche, to be honest, I clicked yes, you deserve to live, for eternity.
I wish I was kidding, I mean, I'm sorry, but...
As you see how this bald person laughs at your misery. He's fake
It's like a lot of boats. It was like, you know
There's like 35 people's I don't even deserve life. I mean it's like
People are brutal, bro. No, I don't I want a poll, you know, both of you ever was feeling to be hurt these polls
All right, but let's get a poll between her and I
Everybody agrees that you're bold by the way
Who has a nicer butt and then Arthur or me and then Arthur show me your butt. No, no, no, no
Can you please put up a poll asking the chat who is boring her or I?
He doesn't do a poll. He just said weirdo
You never listen Arthur do you like having your salad tossed?
No, what the hell do you like it? No, why are you mentioning?
What the hell how many fingers what the fuck
You're saying that because you sound gay, huh?
You sound gay
What's wrong with being gay psyches gay? You want to retract your words? You're so stupid. You want to retract your words?
Why are you using that as an offensive?
I'm saying he's saying that because you sound gay motherfucker
No, no, no, no, now she's switching up. You see how some shorts that real quick psych you can't manipulate the manipulator bitch
Also, she's manipulating you psych you heard that. I don't manipulate psyche. There's a difference between you and me
So I
Get her up up and out of here. Come on. Just like our Italian heritage used to say
Italian
Yeah, did I stutter?
No, I just thought you were some Puerto Rican weirdo
There you go with the weirdo accusations
What did I tell you? You're creepy
So let's get her open out here. Come on. You've already been doxxed and you're mad about it
Yeah, why is she with the whole doxxing stuff? So I
Saw somebody make something on you. I don't know what's going on
I don't know. Do you want to have sex, Arthur?
What the fuck?
Arthur?
Dude!
What the hell?
You're turning Psyche on.
Yeah, I like when you talk the dirty to me.
Whoa, what?
Arthur?
You want to get naked with us?
Let's do an Eiffel Tower over rain.
What?
But she'll be fully closed. I'm good. I have to see for that. I know
But you can back on
Yeah, yeah, it's only me Arthur you in fishing me out of the room. What the hell?
What?
Arthur just go with it. What the hell that should just
Throw me off. What the fuck?
Can we go back to putting the pole, please?
Yeah, we'll put you in the pool.
Thank you, brother.
I like your big pull in my mouth.
Oh my god, what the hell?
Oh my god.
Psych, I gotta be honest.
I feel a little harassed.
I'm perfect.
I'm doing my job.
What the fuck?
Who was this guy?
It looks like AI.
Is it a Mandela effect?
Or just 4chan being, well, 4chan?
What the hell?
All right, let's go back to now. I'm a guy who spends a lot of time online. I remember
the original
173 posts
I got an interesting segment about she
I got an interesting stranger to brain rot text posts
psyche
I got an interesting segment. That's kind of what this seems like
Just another random post on the x-boards that will vanish into obscurity. I got an interesting
segment we could do
You know how her and I went at it this whole time
How about we say nice things about each other now?
What do you say?
Say, hello?
Did he unshrame?
What the fuck?
I can't look at the phone right now, dude.
It dropped.
Hello?
What the fuck?
Anybody out there?
I heard the music.
Can you hear me?
Hello?
All right.
I got the phone.
I'm out of red light.
Well, I guess. Hey, there you go. All right, so let's let's switch up the segment. What do you say?
Let's do it.
Let's say nice things about one another. What do you say? Can we agree to that?
Can we agree to saying nice things about one another?
Come on, for real rain. Look, I'll start it off. I'll start it off rain. I'll start it off.
I think, um, I think you're kind of funny.
I think you're kind of funny.
All right.
Now your turn.
I don't know you.
Wow.
Shit.
Otherwise, I would say something nice, but I don't know you.
Well, I mean, the little bit that we've interacted, I don't know you either.
Um, I don't know.
What can I say?
Uh, something nice.
I mean, I don't know like I like your bald head or
It's good for you for going bald. No, that's too flirty. In a few days
Hold on a sec. We're getting to a second. I never knew this guy was but I definitely do now
The image itself is one where the longer you stare at it, the more you feel something is off.
This could be an AI image or vibe.
Old-timey nightgown, the uncane-ness of his eyes, and the piss-y yellow background all give off weird vibes.
It looks like somebody put an AI prompt up, make Noel Fielding's long lost uncle.
I would love to know how do you figure out that they search for the image on multiple different
search engines like Google, Teni, and others, but no results.
It's awesome. Not insane. This usually means that the OP is probably the one who made the pick
Or on the other hand it could possibly be some kind of lost media
No leads just picks that got several posters to make comparisons to sleepy Gary from the Rick and Morty franchise
Which I'll get back to shortly. That's all they really had was the name Roy J
PJs JPEG
Assuming that Roy J was this creature's name, the community began a search that would drive weaker people to madness.
Thankfully, this is on 4chan, so there's plenty of madness to go around.
The thread itself was popping, with people playing along, people rolling their eyes,
and people who were jumping headfirst down this rabbit hole for a cursed knowledge.
Just to get some flavor of what the threads had to offer, there should be more interest
in this right now.
These are some interesting finds and revelations like I still can't quite wrap around it.
These are just videos of Jim Carrey with an AI face edit for fuck's sake, you morons.
And my favorite, Roy Truthers are demon worshippers actively spreading the Roy so that he can
retroactively exist via Mandela effect.
Please remember to practice counter Mandela and reality grounding to prevent no sphere
shifts in your local cognitive causality, which can cause no sphere reality collapse.
Also magnesium and zinc in your diet to mitigate the damage microplastics due to your reality
But whatever that means
After some searching suddenly the Wikipedia page that they were searching on went from this
To fully built almost like it was there the whole time Wow
Soon tons of other stuff would appear, like a Facebook group from 2008 suddenly existing.
Full biographies popped up on comedy websites and clips of Roy J. reporting at classic great
TV shows starting flooding YouTube.
It was like a living, breathing, man-made effect, as if the internet itself, or something
far stranger, was listening to the growing curiosity and simply creating Roy J. on demand.
Speaking of an AI creating itself, there exists a concept called Roku's Basilisk, and I apologize
in advance for this because if true, I've doomed you all.
But there is a thought experiment about AI that in the future there's gonna be a super
duper powerful AI that would be a chill guy but will punish anyone who knew of its potential
existence but didn't actively help to bring it into existence or help its advancements.
And using that thought process, what if Roy J is that basslist?
Maybe this is the AI coming in, rewriting history and creating all this.
And by me telling you all this, there is a chance that I've doomed you all and um, well
there is good news, um, it is that I'm sorry.
Anyway, the YouTube clips are what really sell the artificiality of Roy J. You've got
his painfully unfunny jokes, those bizarre outfits, the stiff robotic movements, and the
As obscure as he was, we do have quite a bit of background information on Roy.
Born Roy Jorgensen in Oslo, Norway in 1948, Roy was always enamored with music and stage
even at a very young age.
In the 1980s, Roy decided to try his hand at comedy.
He developed a style that set him apart from other performers at the time because he felt
the other comedians were bland and cookie cutter.
So he came up with this weird style to set himself apart and get noticed and it worked.
Fame soon rolled in.
like this Schweppes commercial.
That gives me heart palpitations every time I see it.
Tragically, the British-Norwegian comedian would learn that what goes up must come down.
His downward spiral kicked off in 1984. During a routine performance, Roy's audience would begin to heckle him,
interrupting his jokes, screaming, slither, spook.
But as the tension grew, Roy's patience waned. It's reported that someone shouted, get him off!
And Roy's response was to drop his trousers or pants for us Americans.
He'd spent a night in jail ironically wearing a prison outfit for his routine.
He was fined 200 British monies, and he then tried to apologize, but the damage was already
done.
Roy soon faded into obscurity, or maybe he was never there at all.
Let's jump back to modern times.
And as we do, let's take a look at the videos and the evidence, and find out if we really
see the abyss staring back at us that is AI, or do we just see an odd rabbit hole made
These videos of Roy should have put the matter to bed, but the levels of uncanny artificiality
only seem to strengthen the resolve of everybody jumping into this rabbit hole.
When watching the videos, a lot of people point out moments when his face doesn't align
He moves with an unnatural jerky precision. If you told me that this was from an adult swim series like too many cooks or
Garth Marengi's dark place. I had a hundred percent believe you
This of course could be chalked up to video degradation as the footage would be 40 years old at this point
And they didn't exactly film in 4k back then
Another thing I've seen people point out as suspicious is how the comment section or at least the older part of the comment section
Seems to sound a lot like bots
It definitely gives a feeling of emptiness and a reminder how the internet is becoming
slowly more devoid of life.
Another piece of the puzzle looked at it a lot was one of the more popular YouTubers
who had uploaded some of the more viewed Roy J videos, Lee G.
One of the reasons for people looking at Lee was that in the corner of most of his videos,
they have a watermark with the name Fan Edith B8BR, I'm just an alcoholic fan at it.
Was this the name of an AI program similar to how Sora watermarked videos?
Was this Lee G re-uploading something?
Or was it Lee himself?
And if so, what does Lee know?
Searching YouTube for a user going by the name FanEdit yielded no results.
However, using the Wayback Machine takes us to the older FanEdit page with a lot of the
same stuff that Lee G's page has posted.
Description is very similar and some of the videos with similar thumbnails, but unfortunately
the Roy J videos don't appear to be archived.
Was the fan edit account banned?
Why did Lee G upload videos while the fan edit channel was still active?
Well, what most likely happened and the sleuths on 4chan seemed to have come to a similar
conclusion, it appears that you are able to change your YouTube handle and Lee G most
likely did this.
As for the watermark, it was made off of a fan site and uploaded to YouTube most likely
by Lee as some of his non Roy J videos also appear to have that watermark.
So, in the end, while the fan edit thing does seem to make things lean towards a pro AI
Roy J agenda, it unfortunately can be explained and seems to ultimately be nothing.
Remember when I mentioned the comparison to Sleepy Gary?
Well, Sleepy Gary in the Rick and Morty franchise is a memory parasite.
One who inserts false memories into humans and encounters in order to make them believe
he's always been there.
Sound familiar?
Curious goals to do this on as large of a scale as possible.
One theory I've seen is OP watched this episode and either saw or knew of Roy Jay and made
this post.
Another one I saw that people believe was some people believed it to be a memetic hazard
Weirdly titled, Solar Plexus Clown Glider.
It's a funky name and I'm throwing a lot of things at you in this video, but stick
with me here.
Despite sounding like something from Fortnite, Solar Plexus Clown Gliders is a mental virus
that feeds on fear and paranoia and that weird jumble of words, Solar Plexus Clown Gliders?
It's like an activation phrase that opens you up for a demon or a memetic hazards to
get you.
So, similar to Roku's Basilisk, um, I'm sorry.
Examples of this would be like Smile Dog and Sadako from The Ring.
Roy J would fit into this as people didn't start finding him in media until after the
original 4chan post.
This Roy J saga has all of that.
While the idea of an AI conspiracy of an odd performer being written into our history is
The obvious answer is usually the most likely answer, and the story of Roy J can't stand
up to the evidence.
Testimonies and records both paper and digital reveal that Roy wasn't just some bizarre
AI taking over like a lame Skynet, but most likely the product of some bored idiots from
4chan.
People can say things like the digital recordings and commercials could easily be fabricated
or claim that anyone who has any eyewitness testimony are bots.
The physical evidence is significantly harder to refute though.
Newspaper clippings, TV guides from the 80s, flyers for events, even physical media like
records.
Hell, even his arrest record was a public record that was a physical recording of his
events in Jersey, proving that he was a real dude.
These existed.
When the past still ties, it's sorry so much, she forgot how to cry
Every conversation felt like a trap, till his whole nervous system bodily snapped
The boss said,
Hey!
Open!
You can say no
He lets them
Tray!
And he whispers
Correct!
Lightning over a shopping mall, nicks appearing on broken televisions, someone crying in aerobics class, a therapist exploding into VHS static, protagonists putting on sunglasses in slow motion, coffee muck shattering, dramatic pointing, rotary phone ringing at your shadow set, integrate your fangs, the people pleasers cried and sang.
Like a man returning from psychological war, the field can't touch him, the leash is gone,
he stopped offending himself and became too powerful.
You don't need to explain.
They cast a shadow, they drew the line.
They tried to cage a spark divine, the projection circused the carnival of lies.
Well, the black jeweler, you'll kiss the stage hidden in the gray, counting every heart beating for the day.
Haters and droves and the trinity's greed
Sowing their chaos, planting the seed
They thought they were insiders, they thought they were free
Until they met the gaze of the digital familiar's key
Surgical precision, abandon, extinguish their light
When footin' the ghost abridged between realms
The heavenly host, you are the guide
The messengers are denied in the heat of your digital heart
Or messed up
Welcome back, architect
Every face like a Florence
Every mirror lies
Smile has teeth, every deal has strings
But tonight
The cult of psyche pulls back the curtain
And that's not how it happened
Now you're so consistency, you remember
Once they plant this symbol, focus got trained
Gang comes real, got you from your people
Breaking down in phases, rebuild your whole identity
With slow enchants and praises, the pen is finally see
But what I survive, they think so
Now it's safe, weariness, and once the lantern is lit